<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  >


<channel>

  <title>
Fermilab at Work</title>

  <link href="http://news.fnal.gov/rss-faw" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

  <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

  <!-- Feed Logo (optional) -->

    <image>

      <url>
http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/themes/fermilab-newsroom/img/icons/fnal-logomark-blue.png</url>

      <title>

        The latest news from News Center.      </title>

      <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

    </image>

  <description>
Fermilab news</description>


  <language>
en-US</language>

  <updatePeriod>
hourly</updatePeriod>

  <updateFrequency>
1</updateFrequency>

  <generator>
https://wordpress.org/?v=4.4.2</generator>

  <item>

    <title>
Citrus sunset</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/citrus-sunset/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 31 Mar 2016 08:00:16 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36730</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Plum-colored clouds drift through a grapefruit sky. ]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_36724" style="width: 970px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/grapefruit-plum-sky.jpg">
<img class="size-full wp-image-36724" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/grapefruit-plum-sky.jpg" alt="Plum-colored clouds drift through a grapefruit sky. Photo: Amy Scroggins, Abri Credit Union" width="960" height="720" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/grapefruit-plum-sky-300x225.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/grapefruit-plum-sky-768x576.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/grapefruit-plum-sky-450x338.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/grapefruit-plum-sky.jpg 960w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Plum-colored clouds drift through a grapefruit sky. Photo: Amy Scroggins, Abri Credit Union</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Video: Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi visits Fermilab</title>

    <link>
https://youtu.be/iNNgGGZETm8</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 31 Mar 2016 01:51:04 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Video]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37286</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[On March 30, 2016, Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi visited Fermilab and talked with researchers about Italy’s many important contributions to the laboratory’s scientific programs.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[On March 30, 2016, Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi visited Fermilab and talked with researchers about Italy’s many important contributions to the laboratory’s scientific programs.]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Prime Minister of Italy visits Fermilab</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/prime-minister-italy-visits-fermilab/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 30 Mar 2016 22:38:51 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[News you need]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Top News]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37253</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Fermilab welcomes Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi and celebrates nearly four decades of partnership and cooperation.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Today Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi visited Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory to celebrate nearly four decades of collaboration between Fermilab and Italy. Renzi met with Fermilab Director Nigel Lockyer and Italian researchers to discuss the many contributions Italy &mdash; and Italian scientists, engineers and students &mdash; have made and continue to make to Fermilab and to particle physics research.</p>

<p>
While at Fermilab, Renzi toured an operations center that serves as a hub for Fermilab’s neutrino experiments and a technical area where high-tech, Italian-made particle accelerator components are assembled.</p>

<p>
“The world of research is now global and interconnected,” Renzi said, addressing a group of about 50 Italian scientists, engineers and students gathered to welcome him to the lab.</p>

<p>
As a significant contingent on Fermilab’s CDF experiment, Italian scientists were among those who discovered the top quark in 1995. It was a major success of the relationship with the Italian National Institute of Nuclear Physics, or INFN, that started in the early 1980s.</p>

<p>
“Our involvement is not only at the level of the physics, but also at technology, and also our industry,” said INFN Vice President for Research Antonio Masiero. “We think that, working together, we can have a mutual benefit from both institutions.”</p>

<div id="attachment_37235" style="width: 1034px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit107.jpg">
<img class="size-large wp-image-37235" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit107-1024x722.jpg" alt="Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi (center) tours the Remote Operations Center West at Fermilab and learns about neutrinos. Photo: Fermilab" width="1024" height="722" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit107-300x212.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit107-768x542.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit107-1024x722.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit107-450x317.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit107-250x176.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi (center) tours the Remote Operations Center West at Fermilab and learns about neutrinos. Photo: Fermilab</p>
</div>

<p>
Fermilab scientist Luciano Ristori noted that one of Italy’s – and the world’s – great physicists made an important contribution to the laboratory in nothing less than its very name.</p>

<p>
“We are all extremely proud of the fact that this important American research laboratory is named after the great Italian Enrico Fermi,” Ristori said, addressing Prime Minister Renzi.</p>

<p>
Prime Minister Renzi was accompanied by Italian officials including Ambassador Armando Varricchio, Deputy Minister of Economic Development Ivan Scalfarotto, and Consul General of Italy in Chicago Adriano Monti. Prominent scientists from Italy traveled to Fermilab to celebrate the occasion, including Carlo Rubbia, a Nobel Prize-winning physicist, senator-for-life of the Italian Republic and former director general of the European laboratory CERN; Antonio Masiero, INFN vice president for research; and Sergio Bertolucci, INFN coordinator for the future Deep Underground Neutrino Experiment, or DUNE, to be hosted by Fermilab.</p>

<p>
Italian contributions to Fermilab are felt throughout the laboratory’s R&amp;D programs. Rubbia developed the revolutionary liquid-argon detector technology behind several Fermilab neutrino experiments, including the flagship experiment DUNE, enabling researchers to study neutrino interactions in a new way.</p>

<p>
“Fermilab helps CERN bring forward its flagship program, the LHC,” Bertolucci said. “CERN helps Fermilab to bring forward its flagship program, DUNE. And all the funding agencies, like INFN in Italy, they are working on both projects. It’s a nice synergy.”</p>

<p>
Italian institutions have strong, ongoing partnerships with DUNE, its supporting Long-Baseline Neutrino Facility and Fermilab’s Short-Baseline Neutrino Program. Fermilab will reuse the detector for Rubbia’s ICARUS neutrino experiment, being upgraded at European laboratory CERN, which ran at the Italian Gran Sasso Laboratory from 2010-14.</p>

<div id="attachment_37241" style="width: 1034px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit104.jpg">
<img class="size-large wp-image-37241" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit104-1024x762.jpg" alt="Fermilab scientist Anna Grassellino explains accelerator technology on display at the laboratory's Technical Campus to Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi. Photo: Fermilab" width="1024" height="762" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit104-300x223.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit104-768x571.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit104-1024x762.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit104-450x335.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Itialian_PM_visit104-250x186.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Fermilab scientist Anna Grassellino explains accelerator technology on display at the laboratory&#8217;s Technical Campus to Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi. Photo: Fermilab</p>
</div>

<p>
“Italy is the beginning of a story, which is becoming a major American story, with neutrinos,&#8221; Rubbia said. &#8220;So I&#8217;m very happy to see how things are developing.&#8221;</p>

<p>
Italy also plays a major role in Fermilab’s accelerator R&amp;D. The Italian company Ettore Zanon is one of the few in the world capable of manufacturing the superconducting cavities – structures that impart energy to particle beams – designed at Fermilab for next-generation accelerators.</p>

<p>
The superconducting magnets that will be used in Fermilab’s Mu2e experiment were designed in a fruitful collaboration between Fermilab and INFN Genoa. The partnership has yielded prototypes that can produce a magnetic field 20 times stronger than their current counterparts.</p>

<p>
Young Italian scientists and engineers have had a major positive impact on Fermilab research, including advances made by interns who come to Fermilab through the Italian Graduate Students summer program, which has seen 400 students study at Fermilab over its 30-year history.</p>

<p>
“You find at Fermilab that of 2,000 people, 130 are Italians,” Renzi said. “Research teams here are headed by Italians, and they are doing a great job. The important thing for us is to give Italians the opportunity not only to show the value of ‘made in Italy’ technology, but also to show the skills Italians learn in Italy. Most of these people graduated from Italian universities.”</p>

<p>
Before departing Fermilab, Renzi met many members of Fermilab’s Italian community, including scientists, engineers, technicians and students, who will continue to strengthen the bonds between the laboratory and Italy into the future.</p>

<p>
“There’s a special relationship between Italy and the U.S., and in particular between the science that’s taking place in Europe, at CERN, at Gran Sasso and also at Fermilab,” Lockyer said. “The Prime Minister said he could feel the passion for our science here. The future is looking great.”</p>

<p>
<em>
<a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/134273042@N07/albums/72157666465885201">
View photos of the visit on Fermilab&#8217;s flickr</a>
.</em>
</p>

<p>
<em>
<a href="https://youtu.be/iNNgGGZETm8">
View a four-minute video of highlights from the visit</a>
.</em>
</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Bonnie Fleming is new deputy chief research officer for neutrino science</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/bonnie-fleming-new-deputy-chief-research-officer-neutrino-science/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 30 Mar 2016 19:56:40 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[News you need]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37193</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The new directorate-level position focuses on the international Deep Underground Neutrino Experiment and the Short-Baseline Neutrino Program.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_35371" style="width: 160px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/fleming-11-0211-18D.jpg">
<img class="size-full wp-image-35371" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/fleming-11-0211-18D.jpg" alt="Bonnie Fleming" width="150" height="225" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
<center>
Bonnie Fleming</center>
</p>
</div>

<p>
The strategic plan for U.S. particle physics, captured in the 2014 P5 report, strongly recommended the national pursuit of neutrino physics, calling it one of the five science drivers for particle physics research in the United States.</p>

<p>
In recognition of the importance of neutrino science to Fermilab’s mission, Director Nigel Lockyer recently created a new, neutrino-focused directorate-level position: deputy chief research officer overseeing the Deep Underground Neutrino Experiment and the Short-Baseline Neutrino Program.</p>

<p>
On Jan. 1, scientist Bonnie Fleming stepped into the new role.</p>

<p>
Fleming has long been a part of the Fermilab community, having worked on Fermilab experiments since 1997. She is currently co-spokesperson for the MicroBooNE experiment and a professor at Yale University. Previously she served as spokesperson for ArgoNeuT, a neutrino R&amp;D experiment.</p>

<p>
“We want people to know that Fermilab is the neutrino capital of the world and that our efforts in neutrino physics are truly international,” Fleming said.</p>

<p>
As deputy CRO for the lab’s Short-Baseline Neutrino Program and DUNE, Fleming will work to gather support for Fermilab neutrino experiments from scientists and decision makers around the world, including the neutrino community, Congress, federal agencies and the public.</p>

<p>
She takes over part of the previous responsibilities of Greg Bock, who was until last year the laboratory’s sole deputy CRO. With the introduction of Fleming’s position, Bock will be able to focus on other important research areas: LHC, muon experiments and projects, and the cosmic frontier. Both work under the supervision of Deputy Director Joe Lykken.</p>

<p>
“I am thrilled about Bonnie moving into this new role,” Lykken said. “We worked closely together on the P5 committee, so I am acutely aware of Bonnie’s broad view of particle physics and commitment to the P5 plan.”</p>

<p>
Only a few months into the new job, Fleming has already helped establish the <a href="http://npc.fnal.gov/">
Neutrino Physics Center</a>
, which she co-coordinates with Fermilab scientists Deborah Harris and Stephen Parke. The NPC will enable researchers from around the world to participate in Fermilab’s expanding neutrino program.</p>

<p>
“She is a visionary scientist whose international stature and forward-looking achievements are an inspiration for what we are trying to accomplish more generally with this laboratory,” Lykken said.</p>

<p>
Fleming said that carrying out Fermilab’s mission is as much about forming connections as it is about doing excellent science.</p>

<p>
“I’m excited to represent neutrino science on behalf of the laboratory,” she said. “It’s a pleasure to be part of making it happen.”</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Lunch &#038; Learn: Change your legs. Change your life.</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/lunch-learn-change-legs-change-life/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 30 Mar 2016 19:53:50 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[jkoester]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=37175</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[You don’t have to live with unattractive and painful veins. Attend this seminar and learn about treatment for a wide variety of vein issues. Vein specialists will identify the causes of vein issues and provide effective non-surgical solutions. Lunch provided for first 20 to RSVP. Hosted by Vein Clinics of America on Wednesday, April 13, Wilson Hall, Curia II, 12-1pm. RSVP by April 6 to jecker@fnal.gov or x2548.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
You don’t have to live with unattractive and painful veins. Attend this seminar and learn about treatment for a wide variety of vein issues. Vein specialists will identify the causes of vein issues and provide effective non-surgical solutions. Lunch provided for first 20 to RSVP. Hosted by Vein Clinics of America on Wednesday, April 13, Wilson Hall, Curia II, 12-1pm. RSVP by April 6 to j<a href="mailto:ecker@fnal.gov">
ecker@fnal.gov</a>
 or x2548.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Video: Quantum electrodynamics: theory</title>

    <link>
https://youtu.be/hHTWBc14-mk</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 30 Mar 2016 19:26:09 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Video]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37172</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Don Lincoln gives an overview of quantum electrodynamics, the most accurate scientific theory ever devised.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[Don Lincoln gives an overview of quantum electrodynamics, the most accurate scientific theory ever devised.]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Adobe Shockwave Player removal from Windows PCs Thursday, March 31</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/adobe-shockwave-player-removal-windows-pcs-thursday-march-31/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 30 Mar 2016 14:09:28 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[hward]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=37130</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The Core Computing Division will be removing Adobe Shockwave Player from all Fermilab-owned centrally managed Windows PCs, excluding Accelerator Division PCs, starting on Thursday, March 31, at 11 a.m. In addition to posing potential security risks, Adobe Shockwave Player is no longer in use and has caused sporadic issues with Internet Explorer. This maintenance should be transparent and does not require any action. Please contact the Service Desk if you have any questions.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
The Core Computing Division will be removing Adobe Shockwave Player from all Fermilab-owned centrally managed Windows PCs, excluding Accelerator Division PCs, starting on Thursday, March 31, at 11 a.m. In addition to posing potential security risks, Adobe Shockwave Player is no longer in use and has caused sporadic issues with Internet Explorer. This maintenance should be transparent and does not require any action. Please contact the Service Desk if you have any questions.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Symantec client upgrade starting Wednesday, March 30</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/symantec-client-upgrade-starting-wednesday-march-30/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 30 Mar 2016 14:08:49 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[hward]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=37127</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The Core Computing Division will be upgrading the Symantec client, which is responsible for software security and antivirus protection, on all Fermilab-owned Windows desktops and laptops. Servers and Accelerator Division computers will not be included in this upgrade. The upgrade will take place from Wednesday, March 30 at 11 a.m. through Thursday, April 7, at 5 p.m. This upgrade will run in the background and is expected to be nondisruptive. If you have any questions, please contact the Service Desk.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
The Core Computing Division will be upgrading the Symantec client, which is responsible for software security and antivirus protection, on all Fermilab-owned Windows desktops and laptops. Servers and Accelerator Division computers will not be included in this upgrade. The upgrade will take place from Wednesday, March 30 at 11 a.m. through Thursday, April 7, at 5 p.m. This upgrade will run in the background and is expected to be nondisruptive. If you have any questions, please contact the Service Desk.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Time for prairie renewal</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/time-prairie-renewal/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 30 Mar 2016 08:00:30 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[georgia]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=36418</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[This photo of a prairie burn was taken on the afternoon of March 20, across the road from the bison.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_36421" style="width: 1290px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56efec9eba2e1_PrairieBurn.jpg">
<img class="size-full wp-image-36421" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56efec9eba2e1_PrairieBurn.jpg" alt="This photo of a prairie burn was taken on the afternoon of March 20, across the road from the bison. Photo: Georgia Schwender, OC" width="1280" height="854" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56efec9eba2e1_PrairieBurn-300x200.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56efec9eba2e1_PrairieBurn-768x512.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56efec9eba2e1_PrairieBurn-1024x683.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56efec9eba2e1_PrairieBurn-450x300.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56efec9eba2e1_PrairieBurn-250x167.jpg 250w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56efec9eba2e1_PrairieBurn.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
This photo of a prairie burn was taken on the afternoon of March 20, across the road from the bison. Photo: Georgia Schwender, OC</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
The Milky Way’s hot spot</title>

    <link>
http://www.symmetrymagazine.org/article/the-milky-ways-hot-spot</link>

    <pubDate>
Tue, 29 Mar 2016 19:40:38 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Symmetry]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37133</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The center of our galaxy is a busy place. But it might be one of the best sites to hunt for dark matter.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[The center of our galaxy is a busy place. But it might be one of the best sites to hunt for dark matter.]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

  </channel>

</rss>
