<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  >


<channel>

  <title>
Fermilab at Work</title>

  <link href="http://news.fnal.gov/rss-faw" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

  <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

  <!-- Feed Logo (optional) -->

    <image>

      <url>
http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/themes/fermilab-newsroom/img/icons/fnal-logomark-blue.png</url>

      <title>

        The latest news from News Center.      </title>

      <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

    </image>

  <description>
Fermilab news</description>


  <language>
en-US</language>

  <updatePeriod>
hourly</updatePeriod>

  <updateFrequency>
1</updateFrequency>

  <generator>
https://wordpress.org/?v=4.4.2</generator>

  <item>

    <title>
Retirement seminar &#8211; April 14 at Abri Credit Union, Romeoville branch</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/04/retirement-seminar-april-14-abri-credit-union-romeoville-branch/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 04 Apr 2016 17:27:57 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37692</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Do you have enough income for life? Come find out all solutions and get your questions answered. Seminar open to anyone, Thursday, April 14 from 6:00 &#8211; 7:00 p.m. at Abri Credit Union’s Romeoville Branch. For more information: http://www.abricu.com/home/misc/seminar-information]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Do you have enough income for life? Come find out all solutions and get your questions answered.<br />

Seminar open to anyone, Thursday, April 14 from 6:00 &#8211; 7:00 p.m. at Abri Credit Union’s Romeoville Branch.<br />

For more information: <a href="http://www.abricu.com/home/misc/seminar-information">
http://www.abricu.com/home/misc/seminar-information</a>
</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Putting it all together: Fermilab assembles first cryomodule for LCLS-II</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/04/putting-together-fermilab-assembles-first-cryomodule-lcls-ii/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 04 Apr 2016 17:10:37 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Top News]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37307</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The cryomodule for SLAC’s future light source, LCLS-II, is on schedule to be delivered at the end of the year.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_37313" style="width: 210px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0022-03.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-37313" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0022-03-200x300.jpg" alt="Members of the Fermilab Technical Division line up eight superconducting accelerator cavities to form a cavity string destined for SLAC National Accelerator Laboratory’s LCLS-II. Photo: Reidar Hahn" width="200" height="300" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0022-03-200x300.jpg 200w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0022-03-768x1151.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0022-03-683x1024.jpg 683w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0022-03-300x450.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0022-03.jpg 800w" sizes="(max-width: 200px) 100vw, 200px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Members of the Fermilab Technical Division line up eight superconducting accelerator cavities to form a cavity string destined for SLAC National Accelerator Laboratory’s LCLS-II. Photo: Reidar Hahn</p>
</div>

<p>
In February, a Fermilab team came together to witness a moment they’d looked forward to for over a year. Crew members parted the plastic sheeting at one end of a cleanroom and rolled out on narrow tracks a long string of eight accelerating cavities. It was the first cavity string for <a href="https://portal.slac.stanford.edu/sites/lcls_public/lcls_ii/Pages/default.aspx">
LCLS-II</a>
, which will greatly increase the power and capacity of SLAC’s Linac Coherent Light Source.</p>

<p>
Accelerating cavities are structures that impart energy to a particle beam, and they’re the heart of the cryomodule — a major accelerator section — that Fermilab has designed and is <a href="http://lcls-ii.fnal.gov/">
building for LCLS-II</a>
.</p>

<p>
“It’s a big deal. The cavity string’s all bolted up — it’s beautiful,” said SLAC scientist Marc Ross, LCLS-II cryogenics systems manager. “It’s a concrete step toward LCLS-II’s realization.”</p>

<p>
SLAC’s LCLS-II is a powerful X-ray laser that will allow scientists to glimpse nature’s fundamental processes on an atomic level and ultrafast time scales. Today SLAC <a href="https://www6.slac.stanford.edu/news/2016-04-04-major-upgrade-will-boost-power-worlds-brightest-x-ray-laser.aspx">
announced</a>
 DOE approval of the start of construction for LCLS-II.</p>

<p>
Since the rollout, the Fermilab team has been outfitting the cavity string with cooling equipment, instrumentation and structural support to form the cryomodule. By summer, they will have completed their first one.</p>

<p>
“To me this is a major milestone because it shows that we can do it,” said Camille Ginsburg, the cryomodule team lead for the Fermilab LCLS-II effort. “It represents having tested all of those cavities successfully, finalized the design and put together all the assembly infrastructure that was required.”</p>

<p>
The cryomodule is destined for LCLS-II’s new superconducting linear accelerator. Electrons speeding down the accelerator will generate an almost continuous X-ray laser beam with pulses of up to a million times per second — thousands of times faster than the current LCLS puts out. To be superconducting, the cryomodule’s cavities, made of niobium, must operate at minus 456 degrees Fahrenheit.</p>

<p>
The linear accelerator backbone of LCLS-II comprises 37 cryomodules. Thomas Jefferson National Accelerator Facility in Virginia, another LCLS-II collaborating institution, will build 18 cryomodules of this type. Fermilab is building 17 of these cryomodules plus two that will operate at a higher frequency.</p>

<div id="attachment_37310" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignright">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0066-04.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-37310" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0066-04-300x200.jpg" alt="Andrew Penhollow of the Fermilab Technical Division tends to the LCLS-II prototype cavity string, which is seen here mounted to cooling infrastructure. Photo: Reidar Hahn" width="300" height="200" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0066-04-300x200.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0066-04-768x513.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0066-04-450x300.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0066-04-250x167.jpg 250w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/lcls-ii-16-0066-04.jpg 800w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Andrew Penhollow of the Fermilab Technical Division tends to the LCLS-II prototype cavity string, which is seen here mounted to cooling infrastructure. Photo: Reidar Hahn</p>
</div>

<p>
The boost from a pulsed beam to a continuous one means that the new accelerator will require much more power to operate. And with great power comes the need for great efficiency.</p>

<p>
That’s why Fermilab scientists have, for the better part of a decade, been working on methods for building and treating cavities to be as efficient as they can be. By imparting maximum energy to the beam with minimal energy loss, efficient cavities help drive down the cost.</p>

<p>
Last year, the Fermilab team reported a <a href="http://news.fnal.gov/2015/11/fermilab-attains-unprecedented-quality-factor-for-lcls-ii-accelerator-cavity/">
world-record quality factor</a>
, an indicator of the cavity’s efficiency in minimizing thermal losses.</p>

<p>
“The performance of the individually tested cavities that were put into the string was far beyond anything that has been put into such a cryomodule before,” Ross said.</p>

<p>
Fermilab also designed the cryomodule’s instrumentation to be able to handle the high power and its plumbing system to carry away heat.</p>

<p>
“With continuous-wave operation, there’s a much higher heat load than there is with pulsed-beam acceleration, so everything has to be more robust,” said Fermilab’s Elvin Harms, who leads cryomodule testing for LCLS-II at Fermilab.</p>

<p>
Scientists and engineers specially designed the couplers that transfer the radio-frequency power to the cavities with thicker, high-conductivity plating, for example, to carry away the high heat load.</p>

<p>
The assembly process to this point has been painstaking, said Fermilab scientist Anna Grassellino, who is responsible for cavity preparation and testing for LCLS-II. And it promises to remain that way until the cryomodule is finally delivered to SLAC.</p>

<p>
“Everything that’s happening now with the cryomodule assembly — every step is critical,” Grassellino said. “How you handle the parts can affect performance.”</p>

<p>
Technicians who successfully assembled the first cavity string in the cleanroom spent two weeks carefully putting the components together. Following a protocol established at DESY in Germany and Saclay in France and borne out in tests at the Fermilab Accelerator Science and Technology facility, they moved in slow motion, since too-rapid movements would create particulates that could make their way into the cavity, degrading its operation in an accelerator.</p>

<p>
“These techniques that seem ancillary are actually quite sophisticated,” Grassellino said. “When the cavity string was finished, it was, ‘Phew! Now it’s sealed, now it rolls out.’”</p>

<p>
Crews are carefully installing shielding to protect the cavities from Earth’s magnetic field, which would ruin their performance; welding the cavity string to the plumbing for the super-cooled helium that will keep the cavities cold; and connecting everything structurally inside the vacuum vessel.</p>

<p>
Cryomodule tests will begin early this summer. Fermilab and Jefferson Lab plan to move the completed cryomodules to SLAC toward the end of 2016.</p>

<p>
“Congratulations to the entire cryomodule team here, at Jefferson Lab and at SLAC,” said Rich Stanek, Fermilab LCLS-II senior team leader. “We’re working hard to deliver cryomodules that meet or exceed specifications within the project cost and schedule.”</p>

<p>
LCLS-II, like its predecessor LCLS, will be a DOE Office of Science User Facility.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Windows “Self Service” rollout Tuesday, April 12</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/04/windows-self-service-rollout-tuesday-april-12/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 04 Apr 2016 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[fwang]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=37668</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The Core Computing Division will be rolling out a new Windows service called &#8220;Self Service&#8221;. This service will allow you to use “Software Center”, an application already installed on your Windows computer, to install preapproved software at your discretion. On Tuesday, April 12, at 9 a.m., two software packages (“Mersive Solstice” and “One Drive for Business”) will be available in “Software Center”. More software packages will be added over time. For more information about this new service, read the knowledge... <a class="more-link" href="http://news.fnal.gov/2016/04/windows-self-service-rollout-tuesday-april-12/">
 More &#187;</a>
]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
The Core Computing Division will be rolling out a new Windows service called &#8220;Self Service&#8221;. This service will allow you to use “Software Center”, an application already installed on your Windows computer, to install preapproved software at your discretion. On Tuesday, April 12, at 9 a.m., two software packages (“Mersive Solstice” and “One Drive for Business”) will be available in “Software Center”. More software packages will be added over time. For more information about this new service, read the knowledge base article at <a href="https://fermi.service-now.com/kb_view_customer.do?sysparm_article=KB0011984">
https://fermi.service-now.com/kb_view_customer.do?sysparm_article=KB0011984</a>
</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Users Meeting &#8211; travel funds available</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/04/users-meeting-travel-funds-available/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 04 Apr 2016 14:12:32 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[strauss]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=37650</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The Fermilab Users Executive Committee (UEC) would like to remind you of the upcoming Fermilab User Meeting: http://orgs.fnal.gov/fermilab_users_org/users_mtg/2016/ The deadline for poster abstracts is on April 15. As an incentive, the poster session is judged and the top three posters get a recognition award with a monetary prize. There is only limited space for posters available. We will select the poster presenters, based on their abstract submissions. The Fermilab Users Executive Committee (UEC) is pleased to announce that the Universities... <a class="more-link" href="http://news.fnal.gov/2016/04/users-meeting-travel-funds-available/">
 More &#187;</a>
]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_37653" style="width: 207px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/2016-04-04_570274f738179_UM2016.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-37653" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/2016-04-04_570274f738179_UM2016-197x300.jpg" alt="Users Meeting 2016" width="197" height="300" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/2016-04-04_570274f738179_UM2016-197x300.jpg 197w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/2016-04-04_570274f738179_UM2016-768x1171.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/2016-04-04_570274f738179_UM2016-672x1024.jpg 672w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/2016-04-04_570274f738179_UM2016-450x686.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/2016-04-04_570274f738179_UM2016-164x250.jpg 164w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/2016-04-04_570274f738179_UM2016-300x457.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/2016-04-04_570274f738179_UM2016.jpg 803w" sizes="(max-width: 197px) 100vw, 197px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Users Meeting 2016</p>
</div>

<p>
The Fermilab Users Executive Committee (UEC) would like to remind you of the upcoming Fermilab User Meeting: <a href="http://orgs.fnal.gov/fermilab_users_org/users_mtg/2016/">
http://orgs.fnal.gov/fermilab_users_org/users_mtg/2016/</a>
</p>

<p>
The deadline for poster abstracts is on April 15. As an incentive, the poster session is judged and the top three posters get a recognition award with a monetary prize. There is only limited space for posters available. We will select the poster presenters, based on their abstract submissions.</p>

<p>
The Fermilab Users Executive Committee (UEC) is pleased to announce that the Universities Research Association (URA) is sponsoring travel grants for eligible young scientists to attend the 2016 New Perspectives (June 13-14) and Users Meeting (June 15-16) conferences. Awards will be granted to students and postdocs affiliated with URA institutions and can support travel to/from and room/board at Fermilab during the Users Meeting, as well as additional time at the lab for participants to work on Fermilab sponsored projects.</p>

<p>
Please apply here: <a href="http://goo.gl/forms/YzzoBpsb2g">
http://goo.gl/forms/YzzoBpsb2g</a>
</p>

<p>
Awards are intended for graduate students and postdocs. Preference will be given to participants presenting a talk at New Perspectives or a poster at the Users Meeting. All applications completed by Sunday, April 30, will receive full consideration.</p>

<p>
Please feel free to contact Thomas Strauss (<a href="mailto:strauss@fnal.gov">
strauss@fnal.gov</a>
) with any questions or concerns.</p>

<p>
We hope to see you all soon,</p>

<p>
Bill Louis &#8211; Chair, Fermilab User Executive Committee</p>

<p>
Sarah Lockwitz &#8211; Co-chair, Users Meeting 2016</p>

<p>
Thomas Strauss &#8211; Chair, Users Meeting 2016</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Morning has broken</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/04/morning-broken-2/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 04 Apr 2016 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37082</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Morning breaks over "Broken Symmetry."]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_37085" style="width: 970px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/broken-symmetry-sunrise.jpg" >
<img src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/broken-symmetry-sunrise.jpg" alt="Morning has broken over &quot;Broken Symmetry.&quot; Photo: Amy Scroggins, Abri Credit Union" width="960" height="720" class="size-full wp-image-37085" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/broken-symmetry-sunrise-300x225.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/broken-symmetry-sunrise-768x576.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/broken-symmetry-sunrise-450x338.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/broken-symmetry-sunrise.jpg 960w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Morning has broken over &#8220;Broken Symmetry.&#8221; Photo: Amy Scroggins, Abri Credit Union</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
David Toback re-elected CDF co-spokesperson</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/04/david-toback-re-elected-cdf-co-spokesperson/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 04 Apr 2016 08:00:49 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Milestone]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37400</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[David Toback's drive and dedication to CDF recently earned him a second, two-year term as the experiment's co-spokesperson.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_37403" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/toback-cdf-cospokesperson.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-37403" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/toback-cdf-cospokesperson-300x196.jpg" alt="David Toback" width="300" height="196" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/toback-cdf-cospokesperson-300x196.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/toback-cdf-cospokesperson-768x501.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/toback-cdf-cospokesperson-1024x668.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/toback-cdf-cospokesperson-450x294.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/toback-cdf-cospokesperson-250x163.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
<center>
David Toback</center>
</p>
</div>

<p>
For the past two years, CDF co-spokesperson David Toback has been spurring on CDF scientists to publish their findings in an effort to uncover new physics or yield more precise measurements using data from Tevatron collisions.</p>

<p>
His drive and dedication to CDF recently earned Toback a second term as its co-spokesperson. He will continue to lead the experiment with Giorgio Bellettini.</p>

<p>
“His dedication to completing our analyses is unique,” Bellettini said. “He’s running the entire analysis. It’s very nice, and it helps me and the collaboration enormously.”</p>

<p>
Toback is glad to continue at the helm of the experiment.</p>

<p>
“It’s a wonderful time to be on CDF,” said Toback, who is also a professor of physics at Texas A&amp;M University.</p>

<p>
During his tenure, CDF scientists have been hard at work, having recently published their 694th paper. They’re also a committed and uncommonly active group for one that stopped taking data a number of years ago, Toback said. Indeed, more than 200 people voted in the spokesperson election.</p>

<p>
“Our emphasis has been, &#8216;Get the papers out!&#8217;. I’m really excited and proud of the fact that we’ll get to 700 papers in 2016. We’ve had nearly as many Ph.Ds, as well,” Toback said. “The resilience of the collaboration is really remarkable.”</p>

<p>
Equally pleasing for Toback is the cooperative efforts of both CDF and its sister experiment DZero. The cooperation has been extremely beneficial for the Tevatron program, Toback says, as has his interaction with Bellettini, former CDF co-spokesperson Costas Vellidis, and DZero spokespersons Dmitri Denisov and Paul Grannis.</p>

<p>
“The relations between CDF and DZero are closer than they’ve ever been,” Toback said.</p>

<p>
CDF is proud of its world-leading measurements of the top quark mass and the W boson mass, according to Toback. Both are competitive with the most precise measurements made at CERN’s Large Hadron Collider.</p>

<p>
“I think the CDF data is incredibly rich,” he said. “There’s a wealth of data there.”</p>

<p>
What’s more, CDF can make measurements not possible at the Large Hadron Collider. Unlike the LHC, which collides protons with protons, the Tevatron collided protons and antiprotons, and thus the directions of the postcollision particles are uniquely specified. Those postcollision paths contain information scientists can’t get from the LHC, and the results should be made available, Toback says.</p>

<p>
“If there are papers close to conclusion, David works to get them out,” Bellettini said. “If there are some that are slower in the publication process, he finds out why. He enlists people, does what he can to rescue those papers. He does that daily.”</p>

<p>
Toback will serve a two-year term.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi visits Chicago</title>

    <link>
http://abc7chicago.com/news/italian-prime-minister-matteo-renzi-visits-chicago/1268981/</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 01 Apr 2016 18:23:46 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[In the news]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37604</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[From ABC7 News, March 30, 2016 (with video): The Chicago area hosted a special guest Wednesday as Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi toured parts of the city and the suburbs, including Fermilab. His first official visit to Chicago, it was the first stop in a four-day tour of the United States focused on trade issues between the U.S. and Italy.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[From ABC7 News, March 30, 2016 (with video): The Chicago area hosted a special guest Wednesday as Italian Prime Minister Matteo Renzi toured parts of the city and the suburbs, including Fermilab. His first official visit to Chicago, it was the first stop in a four-day tour of the United States focused on trade issues between the U.S. and Italy.]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Italian prime minister visits Fermilab in Batavia</title>

    <link>
http://www.chicagotribune.com/suburbs/aurora-beacon-news/news/ct-abn-fermilab-italian-prime-minister-st-0331-20160330-story.html</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 01 Apr 2016 18:23:01 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[In the news]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37598</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[From <em>
The Beacon-News</em>
, March 31, 2016: Italian Prime Minister Renzi rolled in to Fermilab on Wednesday with several dozen other Italian citizens to meet with scientists, including some of Italian birth, and tour the campus' Industrial Center Building.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[From <em>
The Beacon-News</em>
, March 31, 2016: Italian Prime Minister Renzi rolled in to Fermilab on Wednesday with several dozen other Italian citizens to meet with scientists, including some of Italian birth, and tour the campus' Industrial Center Building.]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
The mascot exchange program: Fermilab and CERN swap more than research</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/04/mascot-exchange-program-fermilab-cern-swap-research/</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 01 Apr 2016 14:05:46 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37415</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[In a symbolic, historic move, the world's two greatest particle physics laboratories give each other a gift of warm furries.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_37418" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CERN-Globe-Bison.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-37418" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CERN-Globe-Bison-300x207.jpg" alt="A former Fermilab bison is right at home in its new CERN surroundings. Bison was reported to have said the move was worth it to demonstrate strong multi-institutional partnership." width="300" height="207" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CERN-Globe-Bison-300x207.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CERN-Globe-Bison-768x531.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CERN-Globe-Bison-1024x708.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CERN-Globe-Bison-450x311.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
A former Fermilab bison is right at home in its new CERN surroundings. Mr. Bison was reported to have said the move was worth it to demonstrate strong multi-institutional partnership.</p>
</div>

<p>
Fermilab’s future depends on strong, long-lasting ties to labs and universities around the globe. As nothing builds stronger cross-cultural bonds than foreign exchange programs, Fermilab has worked with its strongest partner, CERN, to start the first-ever lab mascot exchange program.</p>

<div id="attachment_37421" style="width: 235px" class="wp-caption alignright">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Fermilab-Sheep.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-37421" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Fermilab-Sheep-225x300.jpg" alt="Sheep may safely graze in the Fermilab Main Ring infield, as this CERN import does. Bonus: They cut the grass." width="225" height="300" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Fermilab-Sheep-225x300.jpg 225w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Fermilab-Sheep-768x1024.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Fermilab-Sheep-450x600.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Fermilab-Sheep-300x400.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Fermilab-Sheep.jpg 800w" sizes="(max-width: 225px) 100vw, 225px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Sheep may safely graze in the Fermilab Main Ring infield, as this CERN import does. Bonus: They cut the grass.</p>
</div>

<p>
Fermilab and CERN will pilot the program starting in July, each sending an animal mascot to the other laboratory for a year. CERN will receive one of Fermilab’s native American bison, which will reside in a specially prepared pen near the Globe of Science and Innovation. CERN chose the highly visible location as a prominent symbol of cooperation between the labs—and to get some brownie points with the Geneva public.</p>

<p>
In return, Fermilab will welcome a &lt;&lt;rouge de l’ouest&gt;&gt; sheep from the herd that grazes at CERN. The sheep will move around the site during the year, wherever FESS determines the need for grass trimming is greatest. If the pilot program proves successful, the 2017-2018 exchange will include goats from Berkeley Lab and black bear from Kamioka Observatory in Japan.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Advice from Auntie Proton: How to find your super partner</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/04/auntie-proton/</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 01 Apr 2016 14:00:51 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=37358</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Dear Auntie Proton: I’m so tired of being alone and feeling incomplete. How do I find my super partner?]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
<em>
Dear Auntie Proton: I think I’m pretty cool. I have some nice curves and some moments where I feel uniquely (almost anomalously?) magnetic. But I still can’t find anyone to bond with. I’m so tired of being alone and feeling incomplete. How do I find my super partner?</em>
</p>

<p>
<em>
-Mighty Unloved, Overly Neglected</em>
</p>

<p>
Dear MUON: I think you need to change your frame of reference. Before you can find a super partner to make tracks with, learn to be happy with yourself, by yourself. There’s no need to be negative about your prospects, MU. Things will only decay with that attitude! Don’t worry so much about when you’ll collide with your match. (Less MU for He, more MU to ME.) Enjoy all the world has to offer, from the atmosphere to deep underground and everywhere in between. Explore new places with a new energy. Connect with friends, families and groups. Try new things, meet new people, and discern what you really want in a partner. But don’t try to keep your heart unbroken — and don’t let anyone string you along. Remember: It’s rare that someone will be lucky enough to find his or her perfect partner right away. Most of us look for that super partner for a long while — and sometimes we never find them. Perhaps the trick is to find a decent partner, share experiences with them, and make something super together. But that’s just my theory.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

  </channel>

</rss>
