<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  >


<channel>

  <title>
Fermilab at Work</title>

  <link href="http://news.fnal.gov/rss-faw" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

  <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

  <!-- Feed Logo (optional) -->

    <image>

      <url>
http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/themes/fermilab-newsroom/img/icons/fnal-logomark-blue.png</url>

      <title>

        The latest news from News Center.      </title>

      <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

    </image>

  <description>
Fermilab news</description>


  <language>
en-US</language>

  <updatePeriod>
hourly</updatePeriod>

  <updateFrequency>
1</updateFrequency>

  <generator>
https://wordpress.org/?v=4.4.2</generator>

  <item>

    <title>
Sunset from Eola</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/sunset-from-eola/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 04 Feb 2016 09:00:21 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=31853</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[This deep red sunset was captured sunset at Fermilab from North Eola Road on Jan. 29.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_31856" style="width: 1234px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/eola-sunset.jpg" >
<img src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/eola-sunset.jpg" alt="This deep red sunset was captured sunset at Fermilab from North Eola Road on Jan. 29. Photo: Gordon Garcia, Bartlett, Illinois" width="1224" height="816" class="size-full wp-image-31856" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/eola-sunset-300x200.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/eola-sunset-768x512.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/eola-sunset-1024x683.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/eola-sunset-450x300.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/eola-sunset-250x167.jpg 250w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/eola-sunset.jpg 1224w" sizes="(max-width: 1224px) 100vw, 1224px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
This deep red sunset was captured sunset at Fermilab from North Eola Road on Jan. 29. Photo: Gordon Garcia, Bartlett, Illinois</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Call for proposals: URA Visiting Scholars at Fermilab Program</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/call-for-proposals-ura-visiting-scholars-at-fermilab-program-3/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 03 Feb 2016 21:30:33 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=32304</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Universities Research Association Inc. (URA) has announced a deadline of Monday, February 29, for the submission of applications for the spring 2016 cycle of awards in the URA Visiting Scholars at Fermilab program. Applicants should anticipate to be notified by the end of March. These awards provide financial support for faculty and students from URA&#8217;s 89 member universities to work at Fermilab for periods of up to one year. URA makes two rounds of awards each year, in the spring... <a class="more-link" href="http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/call-for-proposals-ura-visiting-scholars-at-fermilab-program-3/">
 More &#187;</a>
]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Universities Research Association Inc. (URA) has announced a deadline of Monday, February 29, for the submission of applications for the spring 2016 cycle of awards in the URA Visiting Scholars at Fermilab program. Applicants should anticipate to be notified by the end of March.</p>

<p>
These awards provide financial support for faculty and students from URA&#8217;s 89 member universities to work at Fermilab for periods of up to one year. URA makes two rounds of awards each year, in the spring and fall. The application deadline for the spring 2016 cycle is February 29.</p>

<p>
Proposed visits can range from attendance at conferences or summer schools held at Fermilab to year-long research stays. Support from this program can include transportation costs and local lodging expenses during a series of shorter visits or salary support during a longer visit. Individual awardees may receive up to a maximum of $50,000 in any 12-month period.</p>

<p>
The VSP award program is sponsored by URA. The 89 URA-member universities each contribute $5,000 a year in support of the program. Since its inception, URA has made a total of 282 awards.</p>

<p>
For details on the URA Visiting Scholars at Fermilab Program at Fermilab, including eligibility, application process, award administration, and the names of past award recipients, visit the <a href="http://www.ura-hq.org/awards/ura_visiting_scholars/index.html">
URA Visiting Scholars Program website</a>
.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Accepting applications for 2016 Alvin Tollestrup Award for Postdoctoral Research</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/2016-alvin-tollestrup-award-for-postdoctoral-research/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 03 Feb 2016 21:28:43 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=32298</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Description: Universities Research Association Inc. (URA) will make an award for outstanding work conducted by a postdoctoral research fellow at Fermilab or in collaboration with Fermilab scientists. Alvin Tollestrup will present the award during the 2016 Annual Users’ Meeting. Eligibility: All Ph.D. researchers in non-tenure track or nontenure track equivalent positions at Fermilab or URA member institutions (http://www.ura-hq.org/universities/index.html) or institutions collaborating in Fermilab projects who are within six years of the receipt of their Ph.D. (as of the nomination deadline)... <a class="more-link" href="http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/2016-alvin-tollestrup-award-for-postdoctoral-research/">
 More &#187;</a>
]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
<strong>
Description: </strong>
Universities Research Association Inc. (URA) will make an award for outstanding work conducted by a postdoctoral research fellow at Fermilab or in collaboration with Fermilab scientists. Alvin Tollestrup will present the award during the 2016 Annual Users’ Meeting.</p>

<p>
<strong>
Eligibility: </strong>
All Ph.D. researchers in non-tenure track or nontenure track equivalent positions at Fermilab or URA member institutions (<a href="http://www.ura-hq.org/universities/index.html">
http://www.ura-hq.org/universities/index.html</a>
) or institutions collaborating in Fermilab projects who are within six years of the receipt of their Ph.D. (as of the nomination deadline) are eligible. The work for which the award is made must be performed in conjunction with a Fermilab experiment or project or under the auspices of the Fermilab Theory or Astrophysics Groups.</p>

<p>
<strong>
Nomination: </strong>
Candidates may nominate themselves for the Tollestrup Award. The nomination will consist of a CV and list of publications and invited talks, a written statement (of no more than five pages) from the candidate describing the research and no more than two letters of support from scientists familiar with the work. The research may be conducted in collaboration with others or as part of a larger project. The award is for a particular research project conducted during the nominee’s postdoctoral years demonstrating the nominee’s own scientific insight and creativity. The statement submitted as part of the nomination, and the supporting letters, should focus on that project and the nominee’s contribution to it.</p>

<p>
<strong>
Selection: </strong>
A committee appointed by the Fermilab Director will make the selection of the most outstanding work. The recipient will be notified by May 1, 2016, and will be invited to present the work in a talk at the annual Fermilab Users Meeting. The recipient of the award will receive a certificate of recognition and a check for $4,000 from URA.</p>

<p>
<strong>
Deadline: </strong>
All nomination material should be sent in electronic form (pdf or plain text is preferred) to the email address <a href="mailto:usersoffice@fnal.gov">
usersoffice@fnal.gov </a>
by April 1, 2016.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Seasonal hire program</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/seasonal-hire-program/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 03 Feb 2016 20:55:43 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[kvb]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=32277</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[It’s that time of year again! We are preparing for our seasonal hire program. The Talent Acquisition Department is asking for seasonal personnel requisitions beginning on February 1, 2016. All requisitions must be submitted in FermiWorks. Please see http://fermiworks.fnal.gov/training/CreateJobRequisitionforSeasonalEmployment_05_15_15.pdf for details on how to create a seasonal hire requisition in FermiWorks. The deadline for requisition submission is April 15, 2016. The seasonal employment period runs from May 2 – September 30, 2016. If you have questions regarding the seasonal hire... <a class="more-link" href="http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/seasonal-hire-program/">
 More &#187;</a>
]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
It’s that time of year again! We are preparing for our seasonal hire program. The Talent Acquisition Department is asking for seasonal personnel requisitions beginning on February 1, 2016. All requisitions must be submitted in FermiWorks. Please see <a href="http://fermiworks.fnal.gov/training/CreateJobRequisitionforSeasonalEmployment_05_15_15.pdf">
http://fermiworks.fnal.gov/training/CreateJobRequisitionforSeasonalEmployment_05_15_15.pdf</a>
 for details on how to create a seasonal hire requisition in FermiWorks.</p>

<p>
The deadline for requisition submission is April 15, 2016. The seasonal employment period runs from May 2 – September 30, 2016.</p>

<p>
If you have questions regarding the seasonal hire program, please contact your HR Partner (<a href="http://wdrs.fnal.gov/section/hrpartner.html">
http://wdrs.fnal.gov/section/hrpartner.html</a>
) or Kathleen Venn Bowers at <a href="mailto:kvb@fnal.gov">
kvb@fnal.gov</a>
 or 840-4367.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
2003 BMW K1200GT Touring M/C</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/2003-bmw-k1200gt-touring-mc/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 03 Feb 2016 18:30:45 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[chuckm]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Classifieds]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=32238</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[For your consideration is an adult ridden, immaculate, garage kept, professionally maintained 2003 K1200GT. It’s a 2nd owner with 21K miles. Current 24K service completed by Countryside BMW in 2015. Rider pegs lowered, bars pulled back 2”, Cee Bailey tall windscreen added and large tank bag. Hard bags, heated grips &#38; seat. Power windshield and ABS brakes. BMW cover included. Must see! $6,000. 630-840-3881]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
For your consideration is an adult ridden, immaculate, garage kept, professionally maintained 2003 K1200GT. It’s a 2nd owner with 21K miles. Current 24K service completed by Countryside BMW in 2015. Rider pegs lowered, bars pulled back 2”, Cee Bailey tall windscreen added and large tank bag. Hard bags, heated grips &amp; seat. Power windshield and ABS brakes. BMW cover included. Must see! $6,000. 630-840-3881</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Employee discount for Vaughan Athletic Center in Aurora</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/employee-discount-vaughan-athletic-center-aurora/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 03 Feb 2016 17:41:17 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[jkoester]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=32187</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The Vaughan Athletic Center in Aurora is offering Fermilab employees a corporate rate. If you are currently taking advantage of this corporate rate the time to renew is now. The good news is the rates are the same as they were last year. If you are interested in joining the Vaughan Center it&#8217;s time to sign up. This is a 12-month contract. Please complete the attached Vaughan Athletic Center Membership Agreement and take it the Vaughan Center Membership Desk with... <a class="more-link" href="http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/employee-discount-vaughan-athletic-center-aurora/">
 More &#187;</a>
]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
The Vaughan Athletic Center in Aurora is offering Fermilab employees a corporate rate. If you are currently taking advantage of this corporate rate the time to renew is now. The good news is the rates are the same as they were last year. If you are interested in joining the Vaughan Center it&#8217;s time to sign up. This is a 12-month contract. Please complete the attached Vaughan Athletic Center Membership Agreement and take it the Vaughan Center Membership Desk with your Fermi ID to renew or start a new membership. See attached form for rate info. This is available to you and your immediate family members living in the same household. For more information contact Jeanne in the Wellness Office at <a href="mailto:jecker@fnal.gov">
jecker@fnal.gov</a>
 or x2548.</p>

<p>
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/2016-02-03_56b22aae5813a_VaughanAthleticCenterMembershipAgreement.pdf" rel="">
2016-02-03_56b22aae5813a_VaughanAthleticCenterMembershipAgreement.pdf</a>
</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
All-Office-of-the-COO meeting on Feb. 18</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/all-office-of-the-coo-meeting-on-feb-18/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 03 Feb 2016 16:19:39 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[debseb]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Fermilab at Work]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[News you need]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=32169</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Chief Operating Officer Tim Meyer will hold an all-Office-of-the-COO meeting on Thursday, Feb. 18 from 10 to 11 a.m. in Ramsey Auditorium. Please plan to attend if you are a staff member in the Facilities Engineering Services Section, Workforce Development and Resources Section, Office of the General Counsel, Office of Communication, Office of Campus Strategy and Readiness, Office of Integrated Planning and Performance Management, Office of Partnerships and Technology Transfer, or Illinois Accelerator Research Center. ]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
<a href="mailto:debseb@fnal.gov">
mailto:debseb@fnal.gov</a>
Chief Operating Officer Tim Meyer will hold an all-Office-of-the-COO meeting on Thursday, Feb. 18 from 10 to 11 a.m. in Ramsey Auditorium. Please plan to attend if you are a staff member in the Facilities Engineering Services Section, Workforce Development and Resources Section, Office of the General Counsel, Office of Communication, Office of Campus Strategy and Readiness, Office of Integrated Planning and Performance Management, Office of Partnerships and Technology Transfer, or Illinois Accelerator Research Center. Is there a topic that you’d like Tim to cover? Email your suggestion to <a href="mailto:debseb@fnal.gov">
Deb Sebastia</a>
n in the Office of Communication.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Muon Campus beamline enclosure achieves beneficial occupancy</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/muon-campus-beamline-enclosure-achieves-beneficial-occupancy/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 03 Feb 2016 09:00:29 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=31649</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The lab met a major milestone last month, achieving beneficial occupancy on Dec. 9, for the Muon Campus’ underground beamline enclosure.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
With the Muon g-2 and Mu2e experiments, Fermilab may uncover new physics that could solve discrepancies in the Standard Model, which maps our understanding of physics in the subatomic realm. Fermilab has been building a home for the two experiments – the Muon Campus – which began construction in 2013. It is also preparing for Muon g-2 to take beam in 2017.</p>

<p>
The lab met a major milestone last month, achieving beneficial occupancy on Dec. 9, for the Muon Campus’ underground beamline enclosure. The beamline links the muon experimentation facilities to the Muon Delivery Ring, which delivers beam to the Mu2e experiment. Beneficial occupancy is achieved when basic life safety systems, such as emergency lighting, fire alarms and communications, are in place.</p>

<p>
“That doesn’t mean the building is completely finished,” said Tom Hamernik, a FESS engineer and conventional construction manager for the Mu2e facility and beamline enclosure. “After the laboratory takes beneficial occupancy, there is a substantial period of experimental equipment installation before the facility is ready for experimentation.”</p>

<p>
The Muon Campus’ projected completion is in 2020.</p>

<div id="attachment_31655" style="width: 1034px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Tom_Hamernik-Mu2eConstruction.jpg">
<img class="wp-image-31655 size-large" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Tom_Hamernik-Mu2eConstruction-1024x447.jpg" alt="The Mu2e facility continues construction, south of Wilson Hall and, in this picture, is left of the completed MC-1 building. Both facilities are a part of the Muon Campus, along with the Muon Delivery Ring (not pictured). Photo: Tom Hamernik, FESS" width="1024" height="447" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Tom_Hamernik-Mu2eConstruction-300x131.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Tom_Hamernik-Mu2eConstruction-768x336.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Tom_Hamernik-Mu2eConstruction-1024x447.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Tom_Hamernik-Mu2eConstruction-450x197.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Tom_Hamernik-Mu2eConstruction-250x109.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
The Mu2e facility continues construction, south of Wilson Hall and, in this picture, is left of the completed MC-1 building. Both facilities are a part of the Muon Campus, along with the Muon Delivery Ring (not pictured). Photo: Tom Hamernik, FESS</p>
</div>

<p>
The Muon Campus is south of Wilson Hall, and it will be one of several experimental campuses that use the Recycler accelerator (located in the Main Injector ring). The MC-1 facility on the Muon Campus, which houses the Muon g-2 experiment, and the beamline enclosure are currently the two areas that have beneficial occupancy.</p>

<p>
“We’re at the peak of construction right now,” said Mary Convery, associate division head of the Accelerator Division.</p>

<p>
&nbsp;</p>

<p>
Convery oversees the Muon Campus program, which is broken into several, smaller projects. Most of the construction and civil engineering projects are complete, while the accelerator upgrades and the Mu2e building construction remain.</p>

<p>
The Particle Physics Division’s Alignment Group is using the lab’s beneficial occupancy to create a magnet alignment network inside the Muon Delivery Ring and the new beamline enclosures. The Accelerator Division is installing equipment, such as vacuum components, instrumentation cables, beamline magnets and water cooling systems. This work is beginning now and will continue for more than a year with many other divisions at Fermilab.</p>

<p>
“It’s a lot of coordination between divisions, and it’s turning into a one-lab type of mentality,” said Consolato Gattuso, the Accelerator Division summer shutdown manager and Muon Campus installation coordinator.</p>

<p>
The amount of time and effort that goes into constructing facilities like the Muon Campus can be daunting, Gattuso said. So the construction and installation crews manage their time wisely by planning and tackling each task in bite-sized pieces, keeping them on schedule. But challenges are also bound to arise from many areas in the construction process, since there are multiple, smaller facets to the project.</p>

<p>
The Mu2e building, for example, has many underground spaces, with ceilings as high as 20 feet, that must fit the 80-foot long, S-shaped Mu2e detector and supporting infrastructure.</p>

<div id="attachment_31661" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignright">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/MC-1_EMexperimentfacility-1.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-31661" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/MC-1_EMexperimentfacility-1-300x200.jpg" alt="Underground in the muon beamline enclosure, a peephole is placed in the tunnel so scientists can peer into the experimental hall of the Muon g-2 facility. Muon g-2 houses most of the equipment and the giant electromagnetic storage ring that arrived in 2013 from Brookhaven National Laboratory. Photo: Rashmi Shivni" width="300" height="200" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/MC-1_EMexperimentfacility-1-300x200.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/MC-1_EMexperimentfacility-1-768x512.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/MC-1_EMexperimentfacility-1-1024x683.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/MC-1_EMexperimentfacility-1-450x300.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/MC-1_EMexperimentfacility-1-250x167.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Underground in the muon beamline enclosure, a peephole is placed in the tunnel so scientists can peer into the experimental hall of the Muon g-2 facility. Muon g-2 houses most of the equipment and the giant electromagnetic storage ring that arrived in 2013 from Brookhaven National Laboratory. Photo: Rashmi Shivni</p>
</div>

<p>
“The complex geometry of detailing and designing all the corners and walls, where everything comes together, creates a unique construction challenge for everybody involved,” Hamernik said.</p>

<p>
For Gattuso, the biggest challenge, besides the construction itself, may be planning and scheduling everyone’s tasks.</p>

<p>
“It’s not just having specialized people doing their work, but also knowing the appropriate pace we need to maintain to stay on schedule,” Gattuso said. “There’s a lot of shuffling that happens when we’re talking magnets that weigh somewhere between as little as 600 pounds and as much as 20 tons.”</p>

<p>
Although there is plenty work yet to be done, Fermilab benefits from having a wealth of existing inventory to draw from. For example, the former Antiproton Source (now the Muon Delivery Ring) and approximately 300 of the lab’s magnets are being repurposed for the two muon experiments.</p>

<p>
Construction and beneficial occupancy work are a part of the natural progression of building and innovating, Convery said, where innovation lies in gaining a firmer hold of fleeting particles such as muons.</p>

<p>
“Both experiments will be able to reach higher precision thanks to the new facilities and improved beam delivery that the Muon Campus provides,” she said. “We wouldn’t have these facilities if it weren’t for the many people who came together to make this a reality.”</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Four on the floor</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/02/four-on-the-floor/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 03 Feb 2016 09:00:01 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=31802</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[This quadrupole-dipole Fermilab logo can be found on the floor of the Tevatron tunnel.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_31805" style="width: 970px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-logo-tunnel-floor.jpg" >
<img src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-logo-tunnel-floor.jpg" alt="This quadrupole-dipole Fermilab logo can be found on the floor of the Tevatron tunnel. Photo: Amy Scroggins, Abri Credit Union" width="960" height="720" class="size-full wp-image-31805" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-logo-tunnel-floor-300x225.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-logo-tunnel-floor-768x576.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-logo-tunnel-floor-450x338.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-logo-tunnel-floor.jpg 960w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
This quadrupole-dipole Fermilab logo can be found on the floor of the Tevatron tunnel. Photo: Amy Scroggins, Abri Credit Union</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
This radioactive life</title>

    <link>
http://www.symmetrymagazine.org/article/this-radioactive-life</link>

    <pubDate>
Tue, 02 Feb 2016 20:47:41 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Symmetry]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Top News]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=32055</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Radiation is everywhere. The question is: How much?]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[Radiation is everywhere. The question is: How much?]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

  </channel>

</rss>
