<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  >


<channel>

  <title>
Fermilab at Work</title>

  <link href="http://news.fnal.gov/rss-faw" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

  <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

  <!-- Feed Logo (optional) -->

    <image>

      <url>
http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/themes/fermilab-newsroom/img/icons/fnal-logomark-blue.png</url>

      <title>

        The latest news from News Center.      </title>

      <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

    </image>

  <description>
Fermilab news</description>


  <language>
en-US</language>

  <updatePeriod>
hourly</updatePeriod>

  <updateFrequency>
1</updateFrequency>

  <generator>
https://wordpress.org/?v=4.4.2</generator>

  <item>

    <title>
New tetraquark particle found at Fermilab</title>

    <link>
http://www.iflscience.com/physics/new-particle-four-quarks-found-fermilab</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 04 Mar 2016 19:15:18 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[asalles]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[In the news]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=34854</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[From <em>
IFL Science</em>
, Feb. 27, 2016: Scientists on the DZero experiment have found an incredible new particle that's part of the exotic family of tetraquarks.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[From <em>
IFL Science</em>
, Feb. 27, 2016: Scientists on the DZero experiment have found an incredible new particle that's part of the exotic family of tetraquarks.]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Nominations sought for Employee Advisory Group</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/34839/</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 04 Mar 2016 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[debseb]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Fermilab at Work]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[From the Laboratory]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[News you need]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=34839</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Nominations are now being accepted for new members to serve on the EAG, which provides Fermilab’s senior management with recommendations from an employee perspective. Nominations are due by April 11. Employees are welcome to nominate their colleagues or to self-nominate.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div class="entry-content">

<p>
If you have insights or suggestions that could help improve Fermilab policies and programs, the Employee Advisory Group needs you.</p>

<p>
Nominations are now being accepted for new members to serve on the EAG, which provides Fermilab’s senior management with recommendations from an employee perspective. The committee meets once per month and is regularly joined by several members of the senior management team. Fermilab benefits from the EAG’s formal recommendations, which come after the EAG studies a topic, as well as the extensive discussions of complex issues.</p>

<p>
Nominations are encouraged from all job categories, divisions, sections and centers and from new and long-time employees. Members serve three-year terms, attend monthly meetings and are expected to communicate with their fellow employees about issues under consideration. EAG members spend several hours per month (including monthly meetings) on committee-related work. Nominations are due by April 11. Employees are welcome to nominate their colleagues or to self-nominate.</p>

<p>
<a href="http://www.fnal.gov/faw/EAG/nomination-form2.html" target="_blank">
Nomination forms</a>
 are available online or in the Office of Communication on the atrium level of Wilson Hall. More information about the EAG is available on the <a href="http://www.fnal.gov/faw/EAG/about.html" target="_blank">
EAG website</a>
.</p>

</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
March 7 is the deadline for the University of Chicago Tuition Remission Program</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/march-7-is-the-deadline-for-the-university-of-chicago-tuition-remission-program/</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 04 Mar 2016 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[karlix]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=34779</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The deadline for applying for the University of Chicago Tuition Remission Program for the spring 2016 quarter is March 7. For more information and enrollment forms, contact Karen Karlix at karlix@fnal.gov or visit the website http://wdrs.fnal.gov/train-dev/uchicago.html.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
The deadline for applying for the University of Chicago Tuition Remission Program for the spring 2016 quarter is March 7. For more information and enrollment forms, contact <a href="http://Karen Karlix at karlix@fnal.gov">
Karen Karlix at karlix@fnal.gov </a>
or visit the website <a href="http://wdrs.fnal.gov/train-dev/uchicago.html">
http://wdrs.fnal.gov/train-dev/uchicago.html</a>
.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
FRA Scholarship deadline &#8211; April 1, 2016</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/fra-scholarship-deadline-april-1-2016/</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 04 Mar 2016 17:27:07 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[karlix]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=34776</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Fermi Research Alliance LLC (FRA) offers a number of four-year scholarships to children of regular full-time FRA employees. The scholarship award continues for a maximum of four years provided the student remains in a four-year undergraduate program and maintains satisfactory academic progress. Applications are being accepted through April 1 for the 2016 FRA scholarship awards. For more information or to obtain an application please visit http://wdrs.fnal.gov/train-dev/FRA_scholarship.html. If you have questions, contact Karen Karlix at karlix@fnal.gov.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Fermi Research Alliance LLC (FRA) offers a number of four-year scholarships to children of regular full-time FRA employees. The scholarship award continues for a maximum of four years provided the student remains in a four-year undergraduate program and maintains satisfactory academic progress. Applications are being accepted through April 1 for the 2016 FRA scholarship awards. For more information or to obtain an application please visit <a href="http://wdrs.fnal.gov/train-dev/FRA_scholarship.html">
http://wdrs.fnal.gov/train-dev/FRA_scholarship.html</a>
. If you have questions, contact Karen Karlix at <a href="mailto:karlix@fnal.gov">
karlix@fnal.gov</a>
.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Video: Why I Love Neutrinos &#8211; Sowjanya Gollapinni</title>

    <link>
https://youtu.be/ryL7XebyL-4</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 04 Mar 2016 16:00:26 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Video]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=34752</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Scientist Sowjanya Gollapini is fascinated by neutrinos' flavor-changing ways and their ability to escape detection.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[Scientist Sowjanya Gollapini is fascinated by neutrinos' flavor-changing ways and their ability to escape detection.]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
One minute with Linda Valerio, mechanical engineer</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/one-minute-linda-valerio-mechanical-engineer/</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 04 Mar 2016 14:15:03 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=34650</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Linda Valerio first came to Fermilab as part of the co-op program. Now she's mechanically engineering lots of accelerator designs at the lab.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_34653" style="width: 180px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/linda-valerio.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-34653" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/linda-valerio-170x300.jpg" alt="Linda Valerio is a mechanical engineer by day, orchestral musician by night. Photo: Rashmi Shivni" width="170" height="300" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/linda-valerio-170x300.jpg 170w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/linda-valerio-300x529.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 170px) 100vw, 170px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Linda Valerio is a mechanical engineer by day, orchestral musician by night. Photo: Rashmi Shivni</p>
</div>

<p>
<strong>
What do you do as a mechanical engineer for the lab?</strong>
<br />

On the technical side, I plan all the details for specific accelerator designs. It starts with identifying what is needed, then developing the design, doing calculations, taking measurements and preparing for fabrication and installation. I also do some project planning, or managerial tasks, so then I am more involved with coordinating people, managing our funds and estimating time and labor. It really depends on the project and the production stage it’s in.</p>

<p>
<strong>
How long have you been at Fermilab?</strong>
<br />

It will be 16 years this summer, plus the additional three years I spent here as part of the cooperative education program when I was a student at Marquette University. I actually visited the lab in high school, and I thought it was a great place. When I later saw the posting in the co-op office in college, I remembered how nice it was when I first visited, and that encouraged me to apply.</p>

<p>
<strong>
What did you do as a cooperative education student here?</strong>
<br />

I was here when they were constructing the Main Injector, so that was really great to see. Everybody was very busy constructing the ring, and the lab needed help from students on tracking the progress and with final design tasks. Later in the co-op, when the Main Injector neared completion, I got to re-design a beam instrumentation device called an ion profile monitor, which was a small project perfect for a co-op student.</p>

<p>
<strong>
What projects are you working on right now?</strong>
<br />

After completing installation of the NOvA transfer lines in the Main Injector, I joined the primary beamline team for LBNF/DUNE. That portion of the project is currently on hiatus, so I began working on PXIE before starting a new role as project engineer for hollow electron lens beam collimators proposed for CERN through the US-HiLumi program. I also occasionally support maintenance and upgrade activities in the Main Injector and Recycler, particularly related to the vacuum systems. I’m also a member of the Employee Advisory Group and volunteer for the lab’s education outreach program.</p>

<p>
<strong>
What do you enjoy doing outside of work?</strong>
<br />

I have a young daughter, who keeps me very busy. I love spending time with her and my husband. I go bicycling as much as possible, and I enjoy photography. Aside from that, I also play violin in the DuPage Symphony Orchestra. There are actually a lot of Fermilab people tied to the DSO. Some are musicians, some are members on the board, and some are family of musicians. Over the years it’s been great to see friendly, familiar Fermilab faces at the DSO!</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Lunch outside the Cross Gallery</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/lunch-outside-the-cross-gallery/</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 04 Mar 2016 09:00:10 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[tassotto]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=34449</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[A hungry hawk catches its meal in front of an Accelerator Division window.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
&nbsp;</p>

<div id="attachment_34452" style="width: 2458px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-01_56d617b0cc85c_Hawk.jpg">
<img class="size-full wp-image-34452" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-01_56d617b0cc85c_Hawk.jpg" alt="A hungry hawk catches its meal in front of an Accelerator Division window. Photo: Gianni Tassotto, AD" width="2448" height="3264" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-01_56d617b0cc85c_Hawk-225x300.jpg 225w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-01_56d617b0cc85c_Hawk-768x1024.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-01_56d617b0cc85c_Hawk-450x600.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-01_56d617b0cc85c_Hawk-300x400.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-01_56d617b0cc85c_Hawk.jpg 2448w" sizes="(max-width: 2448px) 100vw, 2448px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
A hungry hawk catches its meal in front of an Accelerator Division window. Photo: Gianni Tassotto, AD</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
LArIAT begins taking data for Run II</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/lariat-begins-taking-data-run-ii/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 03 Mar 2016 20:55:15 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=34635</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The second run of LArIAT is under way, and the liquid-argon detector is already recording beautiful, low-noise events.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_34638" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/evd_lariat_R8125_S44_E11_annotated.png">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-34638" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/evd_lariat_R8125_S44_E11_annotated-300x234.png" alt="Charged pion candidate enters from left; multiple interactions along its path result in additional particles being emitted at interaction points." width="300" height="234" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/evd_lariat_R8125_S44_E11_annotated-300x234.png 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/evd_lariat_R8125_S44_E11_annotated-768x598.png 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/evd_lariat_R8125_S44_E11_annotated-1024x798.png 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/evd_lariat_R8125_S44_E11_annotated-450x351.png 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/evd_lariat_R8125_S44_E11_annotated-250x195.png 250w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/evd_lariat_R8125_S44_E11_annotated.png 1381w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Charged pion candidate enters from left; multiple interactions along its path result in additional particles being emitted at interaction points.</p>
</div>

<p>
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/2013/08/tracking-particles-with-lariat/">
LArIAT</a>
, the Liquid Argon In A Testbeam experiment, has just resumed operation in the MCenter beamline.</p>

<p>
Data-taking for Run II began on schedule, on Feb. 17. As with Run I, the experiment began recording beautiful low-noise events within minutes of turning on LArIAT&#8217;s liquid-argon time projection chamber, as shown in the image. The custom-designed LArTPC electronics used to record these signals in LArIAT are based on the electronics designed for and used by MicroBooNE. The signal-to-noise ratio achieved by these electronics is impressively high, leading to the clean event images recorded by the experiment.</p>

<p>
While collecting Run II data, the collaboration is working to analyze data from Run I. With data from both run periods, the experiment will characterize the response of LArTPCs to charged-particle interactions in the argon, providing important input to current and upcoming LArTPC neutrino experiments such as MicroBooNE, SBN and DUNE.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Fermilab’s stored data reaches 100 petabytes</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/fermilabs-stored-data-reaches-100-petabytes/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 03 Mar 2016 18:56:23 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=34602</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[What <em>
don't</em>
 the members of the Fermilab Data Management and Storage Department do? They're on top of their game, keeping up with changing data storage technology, maintaining mountains of data, and transferring an enormous number of files between user applications and storage disks. ]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_34605" style="width: 235px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/dms-group.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-34605" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/dms-group-225x300.jpg" alt="Data Movement and Storage Department stand in the FCC tape robot room. From left: Alex Kulyavtsev, Yujun Wu, Albert Rossi, Dmitri Litvintsev, Gene Oleynik, John Hendry, Stan Naymola, Tim Messer, Terry Jones, Alexander Moibenko, Chih-Hao Huang, Paul Tader. Not pictured are Gerard Bernabeu and George Szmuksta. Photo courtesy of Hannah Ward, OCIO" width="225" height="300" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/dms-group-225x300.jpg 225w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/dms-group-768x1024.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/dms-group-450x600.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/dms-group-300x400.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 225px) 100vw, 225px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Data Movement and Storage Department stand in the FCC tape robot room. From left: Alex Kulyavtsev, Yujun Wu, Albert Rossi, Dmitri Litvintsev, Gene Oleynik, John Hendry, Stan Naymola, Tim Messer, Terry Jones, Alexander Moibenko, Chih-Hao Huang, Paul Tader. Not pictured are Gerard Bernabeu and George Szmuksta. Photo courtesy of Hannah Ward, OCIO</p>
</div>

<p>
If you have visited the Grid Computing Center and the computer rooms in the Feynman Computing Center, you may be surprised to hear that these rather small spaces hold 100 million of something. As of January, 100 million gigabytes (100 petabytes) of data is stored in the Fermilab computing centers on magnetic tapes, all maintained by the Scientific Computing Division’s Data Movement and Storage Department.</p>

<p>
We have some idea of what a gigabyte is because we know how much data is needed to fill our phones, which, on average, range from eight to 64 gigabytes. But 100 million gigabytes, like 100 million of anything, is hard to imagine. For reference, one petabyte is equivalent to 13.3 years of HD-TV video. In 1995, only 20 petabytes of hard drive space were manufactured. Fifty petabytes is equivalent to the entire written works of humankind in all languages since the beginning of recorded history. To summarize: 100 petabytes of data is a lot!</p>

<p>
The 100 (and counting) petabytes are collected from experiments at Fermilab and at CERN. It can be difficult to predict how much data the experiments will produce at any moment, particularly when they first start up. The DMS Department must therefore be flexible and able to quickly reorganize and move storage resources, which also requires maintaining a sufficient amount of extra resources to account for any unknowns.</p>

<p>
But the data can’t be collected then left unattended. One of the mantras we frequently hear in the current information age is “technology is always changing.” The changing technology associated with data storage helps maintain the data and improve data transfer processes, but keeping up with the changes requires time and effort. Most data at Fermilab is stored in files on magnetic tapes. The tape drives that read the tapes are not supported indefinitely, which means the data must be moved every five to 10 years to new tapes that work with the new, supported tape drives.</p>

<p>
In addition to these periodic upgrades, effort also goes into fixing or replacing tape drives that fail or malfunction. The software to manage these tape systems, enstore, is written at Fermilab and maintained by the DMS Department.</p>

<p>
Along with storing and maintaining a colossal amount of data, the group set a new record for the number of files transferred in one day. The group stores approximately 30 petabytes of data on disk because disk files can be accessed faster than those stored on tape. Fourteen million files were successfully transferred between user applications and the disks in a 24-hour period. The software for this disk storage, dCache, is the open-source product of an international collaboration between the DESY laboratory, the Nordic Data Grid Facility and Fermilab.</p>

<p>
The DMS Department is currently in the process of adding CMS to the list of experiments they support. As part of the addition of CMS, the group is merging with the Distributed Computing Services Operations Department. The newly merged departments hope to fully support CMS by April, which is just in time for CMS to begin taking data – further increasing the amount of data to be stored at Fermilab.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Lexington solid oak locker room bedroom suite for sale</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/lexington-solid-oak-locker-room-bedroom-suite-for-sale/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 03 Mar 2016 15:06:31 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[mccollum]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Classifieds]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=34539</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Perfect for your little sports person. Includes 1 double locker dresser with 3 shelves, 2 slide out wire storage baskets and 2 pull out drawers. One single locker dresser with 3 shelves, 1 slide out wire storage basket and one pull out drawer. Both dressers are connected by a matching light shelf. (bridge) The bridge has wooden pegs to hang caps too!. Also includes 1 locker room dresser with 5 full drawers and one storage area with a drawer. Also,... <a class="more-link" href="http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/lexington-solid-oak-locker-room-bedroom-suite-for-sale/">
 More &#187;</a>
]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Perfect for your little sports person. Includes 1 double locker dresser with 3 shelves, 2 slide out wire storage baskets and 2 pull out drawers. One single locker dresser with 3 shelves, 1 slide out wire storage basket and one pull out drawer. Both dressers are connected by a matching light shelf. (bridge) The bridge has wooden pegs to hang caps too!. Also includes 1 locker room dresser with 5 full drawers and one storage area with a drawer. Also, one combination dual storage cabinets each with one drawer and 3 shelves. Connecting piece has three book shelves. Must see to believe! Email me at <a href="mailto:McCollum@fnal.gov">
McCollum@fnal.gov</a>
. Asking $950 OBO Pick up only (Batavia)</p>

<p>
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d75896970dd_IMG_0002.JPG">
<img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-34545" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d75896970dd_IMG_0002-225x300.jpg" alt="2016-03-02_56d75896970dd_IMG_0002.JPG" width="225" height="300" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d75896970dd_IMG_0002-225x300.jpg 225w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d75896970dd_IMG_0002-450x600.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d75896970dd_IMG_0002-300x400.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d75896970dd_IMG_0002.JPG 480w" sizes="(max-width: 225px) 100vw, 225px" />
</a>
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589696fff_IMG_0003.JPG">
<img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-34542" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589696fff_IMG_0003-300x225.jpg" alt="2016-03-02_56d7589696fff_IMG_0003.JPG" width="300" height="225" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589696fff_IMG_0003-300x225.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589696fff_IMG_0003-450x338.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589696fff_IMG_0003.JPG 640w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589697334_IMG_0022.JPG">
<img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-34554" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589697334_IMG_0022-225x300.jpg" alt="2016-03-02_56d7589697334_IMG_0022.JPG" width="225" height="300" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589697334_IMG_0022-225x300.jpg 225w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589697334_IMG_0022-450x600.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589697334_IMG_0022-300x400.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589697334_IMG_0022.JPG 480w" sizes="(max-width: 225px) 100vw, 225px" />
</a>
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589697270_IMG_0010.JPG">
<img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-34551" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589697270_IMG_0010-300x225.jpg" alt="2016-03-02_56d7589697270_IMG_0010.JPG" width="300" height="225" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589697270_IMG_0010-300x225.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589697270_IMG_0010-450x338.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d7589697270_IMG_0010.JPG 640w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d75896971aa_IMG_0001.JPG">
<img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-34548" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d75896971aa_IMG_0001-300x225.jpg" alt="2016-03-02_56d75896971aa_IMG_0001.JPG" width="300" height="225" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d75896971aa_IMG_0001-300x225.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d75896971aa_IMG_0001-450x338.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-02_56d75896971aa_IMG_0001.JPG 640w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
</p>

<p>
&nbsp;</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

  </channel>

</rss>
