<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  >


<channel>

  <title>
Fermilab at Work</title>

  <link href="http://news.fnal.gov/rss-faw" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

  <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

  <!-- Feed Logo (optional) -->

    <image>

      <url>
http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/themes/fermilab-newsroom/img/icons/fnal-logomark-blue.png</url>

      <title>

        The latest news from News Center.      </title>

      <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

    </image>

  <description>
Fermilab news</description>


  <language>
en-US</language>

  <updatePeriod>
hourly</updatePeriod>

  <updateFrequency>
1</updateFrequency>

  <generator>
https://wordpress.org/?v=4.4.2</generator>

  <item>

    <title>
Collaboration for improved operations: how OPOS supports the experiments</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/collaboration-improved-operations-opos-supports-experiments/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 21 Mar 2016 17:39:45 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36496</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[You might not have heard of the Scientific Computing Division’s Offline Production Operations Service team, but their behind-the-scenes work is essential for many Fermilab experiments.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_36499" style="width: 235px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/opos-team-2016-03.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-36499" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/opos-team-2016-03-225x300.jpg" alt="The current OPOS team, from left: Andres Felipe Alba Hernandez from Colombia, Qiulan Huang from China, Paola Buitrago from Colombia, Vito Di Benedetto from Italy and Tyler Propp from the US. Photo courtesy of the OPOS team" width="225" height="300" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/opos-team-2016-03-225x300.jpg 225w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/opos-team-2016-03-768x1024.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/opos-team-2016-03-450x600.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/opos-team-2016-03-300x400.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 225px) 100vw, 225px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
The current OPOS team, from left: Andres Felipe Alba Hernandez from Colombia, Qiulan Huang from China, Paola Buitrago from Colombia, Vito Di Benedetto from Italy and Tyler Propp from the US. Photo courtesy of the OPOS team</p>
</div>

<p>
You might not have heard of the Scientific Computing Division’s Offline Production Operations Service (OPOS) team, but their behind-the-scenes work is essential for many Fermilab experiments. The team increases the resources of the experiments by efficiently processing jobs, providing the scientists with quality data and increasing the time the scientists have to analyze the data.</p>

<p>
The current OPOS team, which consists of one application physicist and three visiting scientists, was formed in January 2015 under the direction of Anna Mazzacane with the intention of supporting the Intensity Frontier experiments by helping transform the raw data collected by detectors into a format that scientists can interpret to give it a physical meaning. Now, OPOS is working with DUNE, MINERvA, MINOS+ and NOvA. MicroBooNE, which is taking data and has high-priority need for data processing, is one of the next experiments OPOS will take on board.</p>

<p>
The team’s main responsibility is processing jobs to reduce the experiments’ workload, but as Mazzacane explained, that’s far from all OPOS does.</p>

<p>
“Many people think this work is just push the button and you’re done,” Mazzacane said, “but it’s much more than processing jobs on the grid.”</p>

<p>
The success of their work depends on forging relationships both within the team and with experimenters through improved cooperation and communication. The team, having studied at different universities in different countries, including the Institute of High Energy Physics in China, the Universidad de los Andes in Colombia, the Università degli Studi di Napoli Federico II in Italy and the Università del Salento, also in Italy, have practiced cooperation and communication daily to coordinate their skill sets and areas of expertise. This internal effort mirrors the work the team does with the experiments. Mazzacane credits OPOS with creating a bridge between the experiments and Computing in order to use Computing tools to support the experiments, sharing their expertise to increase the efficiency of the production and increasing the manpower of the experiments to achieve the goals of the collaboration on the production side.</p>

<p>
Team members leverage their knowledge to direct the experimenters to the correct Computing staff member, department or tool to more efficiently solve problems and overcome obstacles. In addition, by working with multiple experiments simultaneously, they can look for new ways of utilizing common tools and workflows for increased productivity. And by coupling their knowledge of available resources with their job processing expertise, they can collaborate with newer experiments to help come up with efficient job-processing workflows tailored to the experiment’s needs.</p>

<p>
For job processing&#8211; no small feat considering the number of experiments they support&#8211;team members use a tool created and managed by SCD, the Production Operations Management System, to handle the influx of jobs. OPOS is responsible for scheduling, running and monitoring the large-scale production tasks while providing status updates to the experiment groups. Team members also produce simulated Monte Carlo event samples for the experiments.</p>

<p>
More information about the OPOS team can be found at their <a href="https://cdcvs.fnal.gov/redmine/projects/offline_production_operations_service">
website</a>
.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Vintage settee for sale</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/vintage-settee-sale/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 21 Mar 2016 17:21:36 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[shandvi]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Classifieds]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=36454</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Vintage settee in very good condition, and easy to slipcover. Perfect for apartment or older home. 80&#8243;W, 37&#8243;H, 36&#8243;D Would need to be picked up &#8211; Geneva.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Vintage settee in very good condition, and easy to slipcover. Perfect for apartment or older home. 80&#8243;W, 37&#8243;H, 36&#8243;D Would need to be picked up &#8211; Geneva.</p>

<div id="attachment_36457" style="width: 5322px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56f00d673ab63_VINTAGESETEE.jpg" >
<img src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56f00d673ab63_VINTAGESETEE.jpg" alt="Vintage Settee $100.00" width="5312" height="2988" class="size-full wp-image-36457" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56f00d673ab63_VINTAGESETEE-300x169.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56f00d673ab63_VINTAGESETEE-768x432.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56f00d673ab63_VINTAGESETEE-1024x576.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56f00d673ab63_VINTAGESETEE-450x253.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56f00d673ab63_VINTAGESETEE-250x141.jpg 250w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56f00d673ab63_VINTAGESETEE.jpg 5312w" sizes="(max-width: 5312px) 100vw, 5312px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Vintage Settee $100.00</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Italian courses at the lab</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/italian-courses-lab/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 21 Mar 2016 17:20:40 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[oalatass]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=36466</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The Cultural Association of Italians at Fermilab (CAIF) will be offering lectures of Italian for beginners. The course is FREE! You can find more information about the courses and enrollment in the linked flyer: 2016-03-21_56f025da2c2be_ItalianCourses_Flyer.pdf Ci vediamo presto! (See you soon!)]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
The Cultural Association of Italians at Fermilab (CAIF) will be offering lectures of Italian for beginners. The course is FREE! You can find more information about the courses and enrollment in the linked flyer: <a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-21_56f025da2c2be_ItalianCourses_Flyer.pdf" rel="">
2016-03-21_56f025da2c2be_ItalianCourses_Flyer.pdf</a>
</p>

<p>
Ci vediamo presto! (See you soon!)</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Far out exhibit at Fermilab</title>

    <link>
http://www.nctv17.com/far-out-exhibit-at-fermilab/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 21 Mar 2016 14:23:23 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[asalles]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[In the news]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36433</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[From Naperville Community Television, March 18, 2016: The Art of Darkness exhibit in the Fermilab Art Gallery shows off the capabilities of the Dark Energy Camera. The exhibit runs through April 29. ]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[From Naperville Community Television, March 18, 2016: The Art of Darkness exhibit in the Fermilab Art Gallery shows off the capabilities of the Dark Energy Camera. The exhibit runs through April 29. ]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Far out exhibit at Fermilab</title>

    <link>
http://www.nctv17.com/far-out-exhibit-at-fermilab/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 21 Mar 2016 14:17:04 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[In the news]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36424</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[From Naperville Community Television, March 18, 2016: The photos in a new Fermilab exhibit may seem far out, and that’s because they are.  The “Art of Darkness” display shows off images from the Dark Energy Camera, which was mounted on a telescope in Chile in 2012 to take pictures of large swaths of the southern sky.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[From Naperville Community Television, March 18, 2016: The photos in a new Fermilab exhibit may seem far out, and that’s because they are.  The “Art of Darkness” display shows off images from the Dark Energy Camera, which was mounted on a telescope in Chile in 2012 to take pictures of large swaths of the southern sky.]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Mu2e building construction continues</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/mu2e-building-construction-continues/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 21 Mar 2016 08:00:44 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[hamernik]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=36358</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[This panoramic view of construction on the Mu2e building was taken on a gorgeous St. Patrick's Day.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_36361" style="width: 7732px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-18_56ec5af26136f_2016-03-17_Mu2e_Site_Overview.JPG">
<img class="size-full wp-image-36361" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-18_56ec5af26136f_2016-03-17_Mu2e_Site_Overview.JPG" alt="This panoramic view of construction on the Mu2e building was taken on a gorgeous St. Patrick's Day. Photo: Thomas Hamernik, FESS" width="7722" height="2516" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-18_56ec5af26136f_2016-03-17_Mu2e_Site_Overview-300x98.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-18_56ec5af26136f_2016-03-17_Mu2e_Site_Overview-768x250.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-18_56ec5af26136f_2016-03-17_Mu2e_Site_Overview-1024x334.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-18_56ec5af26136f_2016-03-17_Mu2e_Site_Overview-450x147.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-18_56ec5af26136f_2016-03-17_Mu2e_Site_Overview-250x81.jpg 250w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-18_56ec5af26136f_2016-03-17_Mu2e_Site_Overview.JPG 7722w" sizes="(max-width: 7722px) 100vw, 7722px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
This panoramic view of construction on the Mu2e building was taken on a gorgeous St. Patrick&#8217;s Day. Photo: Thomas Hamernik, FESS</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Sharing common experiences: a retreat for women in STEM</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/sharing-common-experiences-retreat-women-stem/</link>

    <pubDate>
Mon, 21 Mar 2016 08:00:15 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[From the Laboratory]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[News you need]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36334</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[What's it like to be a woman working in a STEM field? About 100 Chicago-area women gathered together for a two-day leadership retreat to discuss the topic and share their experiences. Tanya Levshina of the Scientific Computing Division gives her account of the eye-opening event.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_36340" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/levshina-stem-retreat-1.jpg">
<img class="wp-image-36340 size-medium" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/levshina-stem-retreat-1-300x225.jpg" alt="Pictured are Fermilab attendees of the 2016 Career Development and Leadership Retreat. Front row, from left: Jean Reising (CCD), Tanya Levshina (SCD), Alyssa Miller (AD), Irene Shiu (OCIO), Anadi Canepa (PPD), Mandy Rominsky (PPD). Back row, from left: Nandhini Dhanaraj (LBNF), Anadi Canepa (PPD), Anna Pla-Dalmau (PPD), Christine Ader (AD), Kate Sienkiewicz (FESS), Stephanie Timpone (PPD). " width="300" height="225" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/levshina-stem-retreat-1-300x225.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/levshina-stem-retreat-1-768x576.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/levshina-stem-retreat-1-1024x768.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/levshina-stem-retreat-1-450x338.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Pictured are Fermilab attendees of the 2016 Career Development and Leadership Retreat. Front row, from left: Jean Reising (CCD), Tanya Levshina (SCD), Alyssa Miller (AD), Irene Shiu (OCIO), Anadi Canepa (PPD), Mandy Rominsky (PPD). Back row, from left: Nandhini Dhanaraj (LBNF), Anna Pla-Dalmau (PPD), Christine Ader (AD), Kate Sienkiewicz (FESS), Stephanie Timpone (PPD).</p>
</div>

<p>
Thursday, March 3. Workshop. People are gathering in a big conference room at Hotel Arista in Naperville. The sound system is being tested, and the first slide of a PowerPoint presentation is up on the two big screens. In my 30 years of attending conferences, this event doesn’t seem to stand out from the countless others. Nevertheless, this time I feel uneasy and somewhat out of place. I am in the room with about 100 professional women, and the one lonely man here is a local sound technician. What a difference from a typical computing science conference! I am trying to relax, studying friendly and intelligent-looking women around me. A funny thought crosses my mind: This is probably what men experience at every computing science gathering — being surrounded by others that look like them.</p>

<p>
The Chicago Collaboration for Women in STEM has been organizing the Career Development and Leadership Retreat for the last several years. The event is sponsored by Northwestern University and University of Chicago and attended by women from these universities, as well as Argonne National Laboratory and Fermilab. Fermilab sent 11 women this time around. The variety of interests in this group is impressive: mechanical, electrical and civil engineers, chemists, physicists, astrophysicists, psychologists, microbiologists, neurologists, molecular biologists, geneticists and even several software engineers. The participants’ professional positions range from the Dean of the Kellogg School to associate scientists from the University of Chicago. The two-day retreat includes talks by the invited speakers, panel discussions, group discussions and a lot of conversations during breaks, dinner, breakfast and lunch.</p>

<p>
This year’s presentations were pretty amazing. One was given by Melina Kibbe, who talked about sex bias in biomedical research and her quest to publicize this problem. Her work gained real attention when it first aired on <a href="http://www.pbs.org/video/2365256841/">
60 Minutes</a>
, then picked up by <a href="http://www.cc.com/video-clips/el90zp/the-colbert-report-co-ed-lab-rats">
Stephen Colbert</a>
, and by the end was forced to be addressed by the National Institutes of Health, the FDA and Congress. The panel discussion included three very successful women: the COO of physical science at Argonne, the associate dean of the McCormick School of Engineering and Applied Science from Northwestern, and the former director of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carnegie_Institution_of_Science">
Carnegie Observatories</a>
 in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pasadena,_California">
Pasadena, California</a>
. They shared their life stories, the ups and downs of their careers, and answered a lot of questions about conflict resolutions, dealing with roadblocks in scientific careers, and raising children. Maria Curry-Nkansah, the aforementioned Argonne COO, said that she keeps a special “boasting corner” in her office: The way she boosts her self-esteem when she feels down is to look at all her diplomas and awards.</p>

<p>
The most invigorating part of the retreat was the opportunity to chat with several amazing women who managed to contribute to society in so many different ways: studying humanitarian crisis response in disaster areas, gathering data on juvenile prisoners and the psychiatric impact of incarceration, leading research on type II diabetes in the South Asian immigrant community in Chicago, and many others. To my great surprise, I accidentally bumped into a seismologist who met my father, a geophysicist, when she was a student at the University of Utrecht and he was a professor visiting the Netherlands from the Soviet Union. Small world!</p>

<p>
Through my conversations, I was surprised to find that I shared a lot of common experiences with the other attendees: being a lonely woman in a room full of men who don&#8217;t really take you seriously, suffering from time-to-time from <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Impostor_syndrome">
impostor syndrome</a>
 or trying to find a balance between family and work.</p>

<p>
It was an interesting and exciting day and a half. The only thing I regret was that I didn&#8217;t attend the “dressing for leadership” session. I was told that it was very educational, and the biggest mistake is to wear tops, skirts or pants with pockets.</p>

<p>
<em>
Tanya Levshina is head of the SCD Scientific Distributed Computing Solutions Department.</em>
</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Video: Why I Love Neutrinos &#8211; Mark Thomson</title>

    <link>
https://youtu.be/EgMa7fLVipQ</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 18 Mar 2016 08:00:55 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Video]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36079</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[For DUNE co-spokesperson Mark Thomson, the exciting thing about neutrinos is the possibility of seeing small effects from the differences between neutrinos and antineutrinos, which could point to why the universe is dominated by matter. ]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[For DUNE co-spokesperson Mark Thomson, the exciting thing about neutrinos is the possibility of seeing small effects from the differences between neutrinos and antineutrinos, which could point to why the universe is dominated by matter. ]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Safety leprechaun</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/safety-leprechaun/</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 18 Mar 2016 08:00:55 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36157</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Greg Thompson, ESH&#038;Q, gets into the St. Patrick's Day spirit as the Fermilab safety leprechaun.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_36160" style="width: 177px" class="wp-caption alignnone">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/leprechaun.jpg" >
<img src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/leprechaun-167x300.jpg" alt="leprechaun" width="167" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-36160" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Greg Thompson, ESH&#038;Q, gets into the St. Patrick&#8217;s Day spirit as the Fermilab safety leprechaun. Photo: Jose de la O, ESH&#038;Q</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Fermilab AFS migration to NAS</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/fermilab-afs-migration-nas/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 17 Mar 2016 20:38:41 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[fwang]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=36187</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The Fermilab AFS service will be decommissioned on May 1. All files stored in AFS are being migrated to network-attached storage (NAS). AFS users’ home directories will be migrated in batches. See the AFS migration webpage at http://computing.fnal.gov/nasan/afs-mig for information about the migration, when your home directory will be migrated and what you need to do before and after your AFS home directory migration.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
The Fermilab AFS service will be decommissioned on May 1. All files stored in AFS are being migrated to network-attached storage (NAS). AFS users’ home directories will be migrated in batches. See the AFS migration webpage at <a href="http://computing.fnal.gov/nasan/afs-mig">
http://computing.fnal.gov/nasan/afs-mig</a>
 for information about the migration, when your home directory will be migrated and what you need to do before and after your AFS home directory migration.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

  </channel>

</rss>
