<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  >


<channel>

  <title>
Fermilab at Work</title>

  <link href="http://news.fnal.gov/rss-faw" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

  <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

  <!-- Feed Logo (optional) -->

    <image>

      <url>
http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/themes/fermilab-newsroom/img/icons/fnal-logomark-blue.png</url>

      <title>

        The latest news from News Center.      </title>

      <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

    </image>

  <description>
Fermilab news</description>


  <language>
en-US</language>

  <updatePeriod>
hourly</updatePeriod>

  <updateFrequency>
1</updateFrequency>

  <generator>
https://wordpress.org/?v=4.4.1</generator>

  <item>

    <title>
Space heater recall and space heater safety</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/space-heater-recall-space-heater-safety/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 27 Jan 2016 15:05:16 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[asands]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Safety]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Uncategorized]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=31508</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Check your offices and homes for a Vornado portable space heater.  There is one Vornado space heater that has been recently recalled, and this type space heater was involved in a fire at a national laboratory.  View the recall information and space heater safety information here: http://esh-docdb.fnal.gov/cgi-bin/ShowDocument?docid=3186]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Check your offices and homes for a Vornado portable space heater.  There is one Vornado space heater that has been recently recalled, and this type space heater was involved in a fire at a national laboratory.  View the recall information and space heater safety information here: <a href="http://esh-docdb.fnal.gov/cgi-bin/ShowDocument?docid=3186" target="_blank">
http://esh-docdb.fnal.gov/cgi-bin/ShowDocument?docid=3186</a>
</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Particles and unparticles</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/particles-and-unparticles/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 27 Jan 2016 09:00:59 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Result]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=31049</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[CMS goes looking for unparticles and dark matter, studying events in which a Z boson was created, as well as undetected energy that would be the signal of either a dark matter particle or unparticle escaping.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_31121" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/9414042508_fb91b4088d_z.jpg" >
<img src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/9414042508_fb91b4088d_z-300x200.jpg" alt="Those of us of a certain age will remember an old advertising campaign for 7-Up that was touted as the “uncola.”  Today’s article talks about a clever, but highly speculative, idea called the “unparticle.” Photo: Grant Hutchinson" width="300" height="200" class="size-medium wp-image-31121" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/9414042508_fb91b4088d_z-300x200.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/9414042508_fb91b4088d_z-450x300.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/9414042508_fb91b4088d_z-250x167.jpg 250w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/9414042508_fb91b4088d_z.jpg 640w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Those of us of a certain age will remember an old advertising campaign for 7-Up that was touted as the “uncola.”  Today’s article talks about a clever, but highly speculative, idea called the “unparticle.” Photo: <a href="https://flic.kr/p/fkTqRJ">
Grant Hutchinson</a>
</p>
</div>

<p>
The LHC accelerator is in the business of discovering new things, from particles that are expected (like the Higgs boson) to particles that are sort of expected (like the panoply of particles predicted by supersymmetric models) to particles from something entirely unexpected (like the what-the-heck-is-that moment that changes our theories forever).</p>

<p>
The commonality of all of these potential discoveries is that they include particles. All particles have a fixed mass. So all electrons in the universe have the same mass, as do all muons, pions, protons or any other subatomic particle you can name.</p>

<p>
(This is true no matter how fast the particles are moving, and it’s worth emphasizing this point, as it may not jibe with some readers’ understanding of what happens when a particle’s velocity approaches light speed. You may have heard that the mass of a particle changes as velocity increases. We teach this to people first encountering relativity, but the statement is an illustrative one. What actually changes is the particle’s <em>
inertia</em>
, which is equivalent to mass at low velocities. You can read more about this in a <a href="http://news.fnal.gov/2014/04/proving-special-relativity-episode-2/">
previous column</a>
. So, for a particle, no matter what energy and momentum it has, it must also have a single and specific mass.)</p>

<p>
However, in 2007 scientist Howard Georgi had an idea: Suppose there was a kind of particle that had a mass that wasn’t constant. If you doubled the particle’s energy and momentum, you would double its mass. If you halved the energy, you’d halve the mass. Such a particle wouldn’t have a well-defined mass at all. This kind of particle is called an <em>
unparticle.</em>
</p>

<div id="attachment_31067" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignright">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/CMSResult160122_Analysers01-1.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-31067" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/CMSResult160122_Analysers01-1-300x156.jpg" alt="These physicists contributed to this analysis." width="300" height="156" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/CMSResult160122_Analysers01-1-300x156.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/CMSResult160122_Analysers01-1-768x400.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/CMSResult160122_Analysers01-1-1024x534.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/CMSResult160122_Analysers01-1-250x130.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
These physicists contributed to this analysis.</p>
</div>

<p>
Unparticles are governed by fractal mathematics and are highly speculative. In fact, there is no hint in the data that they must exist, nor is there a compelling theoretical reason why they should. On the other hand, they are possible, and given that we don’t know what theory will supplant the Standard Model, we should be open to all sorts of improbable ideas. We do know that unparticles, if they exist, must interact via known forces only weakly.</p>

<p>
So, of course, CMS went looking for them. In a recent <a href="http://cds.cern.ch/record/2109708/files/arXiv:1511.09375.pdf">
analysis</a>
 that looked for both unparticles and dark matter, scientists studied events in which a Z boson was created, as well as undetected energy that would be the signal of either a dark matter particle or unparticle escaping.</p>

<p>
Sadly, no evidence was observed for either phenomenon. Truthfully, it would have been shocking if unparticles had been observed, but the fact that LHC experiments are looking for even such bizarre possibilities highlights that the scientific community is exploring all viable ideas, hoping to find something that gives us a huge advance in our understanding of the nature of reality.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Snowflakes by Lederman Science Center</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/snowflakes-by-lederman-science-center/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 27 Jan 2016 09:00:28 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=31256</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[These delicate snowflakes fell near the Lederman Science Center on Jan. 20. ]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_31238" style="width: 1681px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-22_56a255c9e5478_Snowflake1.jpg" >
<img src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-22_56a255c9e5478_Snowflake1.jpg" alt="These delicate snowflakes fell near the Lederman Science Center on Jan. 20. Photo: Amanda Freeman" width="1671" height="1671" class="size-full wp-image-31238" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-22_56a255c9e5478_Snowflake1-150x150.jpg 150w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-22_56a255c9e5478_Snowflake1-300x300.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-22_56a255c9e5478_Snowflake1-768x768.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-22_56a255c9e5478_Snowflake1-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-22_56a255c9e5478_Snowflake1-450x450.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-22_56a255c9e5478_Snowflake1-250x250.jpg 250w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-22_56a255c9e5478_Snowflake1.jpg 1671w" sizes="(max-width: 1671px) 100vw, 1671px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
These delicate snowflakes fell near the Lederman Science Center on Jan. 20. Photo: Amanda Freeman</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
The genetic purity and diversity of the Fermilab bison herd</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/the-genetic-purity-and-diversity-of-the-fermilab-bison-herd/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 27 Jan 2016 09:00:23 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=31190</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The Fermilab bison herd, a symbol of the laboratory's pioneering spirit, are genetically pure, with not a bit of cattle genetics in evidence.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_31193" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-bison.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-31193" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-bison-300x200.jpg" alt="Fermilab's bison herd is genetically pure, displaying no evidence of cattle genes. Photo: Rashmi Shivni" width="300" height="200" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-bison-300x200.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-bison-768x512.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-bison-1024x683.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-bison-450x300.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/fermilab-bison-250x167.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Fermilab&#8217;s bison herd is genetically pure, displaying no evidence of cattle genes. Photo: Rashmi Shivni</p>
</div>

<p>
Out in the crisp pastures north of Fermilab’s Main Ring, a herd of winter-coated fluff can be found huddling together and munching on hay in the nippy, January wind. The Fermilab bison &#8211; a spectacle for the community and an icon of the lab’s zeal for discovery &#8211; are a treasure with a lineage that dates back thousands of years.</p>

<p>
However, as the American bison population rapidly declined during the early settlement era, bison were at risk of extinction, and farmers often bred them with other bovine species. So what is the backstory of Fermilab’s bison? Are they purebred, and where do they come from?</p>

<p>
To answer these questions, Fermilab ecologist Ryan Campbell submitted tail hair samples of all 17 of the lab’s animals in October to Texas A&amp;M University for genetic testing.</p>

<p>
“We’ve had these wild bison for years,” Campbell said. “We’re just now finding out that they’re 100 percent bison with no evidence of cattle genes.”</p>

<p>
Back in 1969 when Robert Wilson, the lab’s first director, first brought five bison to the laboratory, testing bison genetics was not a consideration.</p>

<p>
When the Nature Conservancy reintroduced bison to their Nachusa Grasslands site in October 2014, they thought they had the first wild bison born east of the Mississippi River in over 200 years, according to Fermilab Roads and Grounds Manager Dave Shemanske.</p>

<p>
“These groups genetically tested their animals before they brought them in, and we never did that in our 47-year history of receiving the animals,” Shemanske said. “We bought animals from reputable farms, inspected them prior to purchase, and we got kind of lucky with our herd.”</p>

<p>
The DNA Technologies Core Laboratory at TAMU has mapped multiple bovid species genomes, and the Fermilab bison were tested against the national herds that the university previously sampled.</p>

<p>
“This genomic testing technology is relatively new, and I don’t think we ever had a goal to have a ‘pure herd’ until we had scientific research to tell us about its importance,” Campbell said.</p>

<p>
A pure herd is indeed valuable for a prairie ecosystem, as the animals are natural grazers and can tame tall grasses, which easily dominate prairies in the absence of wild bison. They also help create an environment where a variety of species – such as grasshopper sparrows, native butterflies, bees and reptiles – can thrive.</p>

<p>
Fermilab’s bison are considered “wild” because of their genetic purity, Campbell said. Unlike other prairie preserves, Fermilab’s bison are kept on a pasture, not on Fermilab’s prairie land. This is to ensure their safety and the public’s safety when visiting.</p>

<p>
Shemanske said all these factors are important for future purchases of wild bison.</p>

<p>
“We need to test to make sure that any new bison bulls we bring every five to seven years don’t interrupt the genetics of our herd by accidentally introducing cattle genes into them,” he said.</p>

<div id="attachment_31199" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignright">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/bison-heritage-pie-chart.png">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-31199" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/bison-heritage-pie-chart-300x177.png" alt="This chart shows the genomic contributions of eight core U.S. federal herds to the Fermilab bison samples submitted to Texas A&amp;M University. Credit: James Derr, DNA Technologies Core Laboratory, Texas A&amp;M University" width="300" height="177" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/bison-heritage-pie-chart-300x177.png 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/bison-heritage-pie-chart-768x452.png 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/bison-heritage-pie-chart-1024x603.png 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/bison-heritage-pie-chart-450x265.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
This chart shows the genomic contributions of eight core U.S. federal herds to the Fermilab bison samples submitted to Texas A&amp;M University. Credit: James Derr, DNA Technologies Core Laboratory, Texas A&amp;M University</p>
</div>

<p>
The lab’s herd can lay claim not only to genetic purity, but also a lineage that spans the country. Eight federal bison herds throughout the United States are linked to the lab’s bison. Almost half of the genome in the herd sample came from Wind Cave National Park in South Dakota, the same source population as the Nature Conservancy bison.</p>

<p>
“There’s a lot of genetic diversity,” Campbell said.</p>

<p>
Having pure bison genes from multiple, geographical areas can produce offspring that have an advantage against various diseases and that can withstand drastic changes in climate. Shemanske and Campbell plan to continue genetic testing before introducing new individuals, noting its usefulness in ensuring the herd’s diversity.</p>

<p>
Armed with the knowledge that the herd is healthy and wholly bison, Campbell and Shemanske continue to promote the lab’s vision of cultivating an environment in which visitors can still watch and admire one of America’s great grazers.</p>

<p>
“We have a world-class neutrino program here, but we also have a world-class environment,” Shemanske said. “The bison are an important piece of this community.”</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Our imperfect vacuum</title>

    <link>
http://www.symmetrymagazine.org/article/our-imperfect-vacuum</link>

    <pubDate>
Tue, 26 Jan 2016 19:53:02 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Symmetry]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Top News]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=31478</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The emptiest parts of the universe aren’t so empty after all.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[The emptiest parts of the universe aren’t so empty after all.]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Bed for sale</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/bed-for-sale/</link>

    <pubDate>
Tue, 26 Jan 2016 19:49:28 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[lorenz]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Classifieds]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=31427</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Bed frame with under bed storage unit. Full size, hardwood, maple finish. 5 drawer storage unit. Good unit for smaller bedroom. $100.00 or O.B.O. Contact Gary at X-6692 or lorenz@fnal.gov if interested. More pictures available upon request.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Bed frame with under bed storage unit. Full size, hardwood, maple finish. 5 drawer storage unit. Good unit for smaller bedroom. $100.00 or O.B.O. Contact Gary at X-6692 or <a href="mailto:lorenz@fnal.gov">
lorenz@fnal.gov</a>
 if interested. More pictures available upon request.</p>

<div id="attachment_31430" style="width: 234px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-26_56a78ca145cc5_209.JPG" >
<img src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-26_56a78ca145cc5_209-224x300.jpg" alt="Bed frame with storage" width="224" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-31430" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-26_56a78ca145cc5_209-224x300.jpg 224w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-26_56a78ca145cc5_209-768x1028.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-26_56a78ca145cc5_209-765x1024.jpg 765w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-26_56a78ca145cc5_209-450x602.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-26_56a78ca145cc5_209-300x402.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 224px) 100vw, 224px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Bed frame with storage</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Hawk seen on a walk</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/hawk-seen-on-a-walk/</link>

    <pubDate>
Tue, 26 Jan 2016 09:00:18 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=29929</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[This hawk practically flew into the photographer as he was taking a walk one afternoon.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_29908" style="width: 1833px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-05_568c2c82796ad_IMG_9087.JPG">
<img class="wp-image-29908 size-full" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-05_568c2c82796ad_IMG_9087.JPG" alt="This hawk practically flew into the photographer as he was taking a walk one afternoon. Photo: Jeff Artel, WDRS" width="1823" height="925" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-05_568c2c82796ad_IMG_9087-300x152.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-05_568c2c82796ad_IMG_9087-768x390.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-05_568c2c82796ad_IMG_9087-1024x520.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-05_568c2c82796ad_IMG_9087-450x228.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-05_568c2c82796ad_IMG_9087.JPG 1823w" sizes="(max-width: 1823px) 100vw, 1823px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
This hawk practically flew into the photographer as he was taking a walk one afternoon. Photo: Jeff Artel, WDRS</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Fermilab&#8217;s second artist in residence mixes tech and art</title>

    <link>
https://soundcloud.com/wdcbnews/fermi-labs-2nd-artist-in-residence-mixes-tech-and-art</link>

    <pubDate>
Tue, 26 Jan 2016 02:47:15 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[In the news]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=31415</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[From WDCB 90.9, Jan. 25, 2016: Fermilab artist-in-residence Ellen Sandor is no stranger to translating science into visual media. She's worked with Jet Propulsion Laboratory and NASA to visualize the invisible. Now she'll do the same at Fermilab. Listen to this eight-minute radio piece featuring Sandor and Art Gallery curator Georgia Schwender.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[From WDCB 90.9, Jan. 25, 2016: Fermilab artist-in-residence Ellen Sandor is no stranger to translating science into visual media. She's worked with Jet Propulsion Laboratory and NASA to visualize the invisible. Now she'll do the same at Fermilab. Listen to this eight-minute radio piece featuring Sandor and Art Gallery curator Georgia Schwender.]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Jan 28, noon, Fermi Society of Philosophy, Al Brunsting: &#8220;Science and God Existence,&#8221; first talk</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/jan-28-noon-fermi-society-of-philosophy/</link>

    <pubDate>
Tue, 26 Jan 2016 02:19:49 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[burov]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=31376</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Starting Jan 28, we’ll have a series of four talks of Al Brunsting based on his book on science and God&#8217;s existence. Details about the book and its authors are on our website https://fermisocietyofphilosophy.wordpress.com/. Everybody is welcome. Feel free to come with your lunch. Note the room: Racetrack (WH7X). Time is the same as always, 12 noon.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Starting Jan 28, we’ll have a series of four talks of Al Brunsting based on his book on science and God&#8217;s existence. Details about the book and its authors are on our website <a href="https://fermisocietyofphilosophy.wordpress.com/">
https://fermisocietyofphilosophy.wordpress.com/</a>
. Everybody is welcome. Feel free to come with your lunch. Note the room: Racetrack (WH7X). Time is the same as always, 12 noon.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
February wellness</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/february-wellness/</link>

    <pubDate>
Tue, 26 Jan 2016 02:14:34 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[jkoester]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=31139</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Check out February's wellness offerings, including a free Lunch and Learn session on preventing and alleviating neck pain.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-february-wellness.jpg" >
<img src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-february-wellness-102x300.jpg" alt="februarywellness" width="102" height="300" class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-31385" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-february-wellness-102x300.jpg 102w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-february-wellness-768x2259.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-february-wellness-348x1024.jpg 348w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-february-wellness-450x1324.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-february-wellness-85x250.jpg 85w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-february-wellness-300x882.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 102px) 100vw, 102px" />
</a>
</p>

<p>
COMPLIMENTARY WELLNESS</p>

<p>
<strong>
Lunch &amp; Learn</strong>
: Tech Neck<br />

Are electronics a pain in the neck? Technology has improved our lives in many ways. Unfortunately, it may be a detriment to our necks. Spending two-thirds of the day with our necks angled down while we work at computers, text from phones, and play on tablets can lead to chronic neck pain,and result in a more serious long-term condition. Attend this educational workshop about common conditions caused from this repetitive stress. Learn tips to prevent the onset of pain and find relief from the pain and discomfort you might already be experiencing.</p>

<p>
Tuesday, February 23, Curia II: 12-1 p.m. Lunch will be provided. Limited to 25. RSVP by Feb. 22 to <a href="mailto:megan.diehm@airrosti.com">
megan.diehm@airrosti.com</a>
.</p>

<p>
&nbsp;</p>

<p>
FITNESS CLASSES</p>

<p>
<strong>
Mat Pilates</strong>
<br />

Mondays: March 7 – April 18<br />

Fitness Center Exercise Room: 12-12:45pm<br />

Fee: $87 (Register by February 29)</p>

<p>
<strong>
Zumba Fitness</strong>
<br />

Thursdays: March 3 – April 28 (no class 3/31)<br />

Fitness Center Exercise Room: noon-12:45 p.m. Fee: $50 (Register by February 25)</p>

<p>
<strong>
Zumba Toning</strong>
<br />

Tuesdays: March 1 – April 26 (no class March 29)<br />

Fitness Center Exercise Room: noon-12:45 p.m. Fee: $50 (Register by February 23)</p>

<p>
&nbsp;</p>

<p>
EMPLOYEE DISCOUNTS</p>

<p>
<strong>
Fermi Fridays with Chicago Steel Hockey Team</strong>
<br />

Experience Chicagoland’s only Tier 1 Junior Team on Fermilab Fridays (Jan. 29, Feb. 26, March 25, April 8) with the Chicago Steel at the Fox Valley Ice Arena in Geneva! Puck drops at 7:30 p.m. Defense Preferred Tickets are $12 ($16.75 value). Purchase discounted tickets at <a href="http://www.steelgroups.com">
www.steelgroups.com</a>
 and enter password Fermilab. $1.50/ticket processing fee applied to online orders. Tickets purchased on day of game are an additional $2. Contact Dave Campione 855-51-STEEL. <a href="mailto:dcampione@chicagosteelhockeyteam.com">
dcampione@chicagosteelhockeyteam.com</a>
</p>

<p>
<strong>
Regal Cinema &amp; AMC Theater Movie Tickets</strong>
<br />

$9 tickets sold in Wellness Office, WH15W.</p>

<p>
<a href="http://wdrs.fnal.gov/wellness/convenience.html">
http://wdrs.fnal.gov/wellness/convenience.html</a>
</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

  </channel>

</rss>
