<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  >


<channel>

  <title>
Fermilab at Work</title>

  <link href="http://news.fnal.gov/rss-faw" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

  <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

  <!-- Feed Logo (optional) -->

    <image>

      <url>
http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/themes/fermilab-newsroom/img/icons/fnal-logomark-blue.png</url>

      <title>

        The latest news from News Center.      </title>

      <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

    </image>

  <description>
Fermilab news</description>


  <language>
en-US</language>

  <updatePeriod>
hourly</updatePeriod>

  <updateFrequency>
1</updateFrequency>

  <generator>
https://wordpress.org/?v=4.4.2</generator>

  <item>

    <title>
Busy bees</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/busy-bees/</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 25 Mar 2016 08:00:28 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Result]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36673</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[CMS scientists look for four <em>
b</em>
's &#8212; bottom quarks that might point the way to Higgs boson pairs.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_36676" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Figures01.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-36676" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Figures01-300x294.jpg" alt="Events in which four b quarks are found in the CMS detector are candidates for a situation in which a pair of Higgs bosons are made. Finding pairs of Higgs bosons would provide a laboratory to look for new physical phenomena." width="300" height="294" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Figures01-300x294.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Figures01-768x754.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Figures01-1024x1005.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Figures01-250x245.jpg 250w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Figures01.jpg 1223w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Events in which four <em>
b</em>
 quarks are found in the CMS detector are candidates for a situation in which a pair of Higgs bosons are made. Finding pairs of Higgs bosons would provide a laboratory to look for new physical phenomena.</p>
</div>

<p>
It was only four years ago when the Higgs boson was discovered; after a search spanning nearly half a century, the Standard Model was complete.</p>

<p>
The Higgs boson or, more accurately, the Higgs field gives fundamental subatomic particles their mass. Because of that, the Higgs boson preferentially interacts with heavier particles. Accordingly, LHC scientists probe their data, looking for something that points us toward a new theory that supersedes the Standard Model. As they probe higher and higher energies, it is expected that we might find new particles with even higher masses. And, since the Higgs boson interacts with massive particles, it seems reasonable that looking for a particle that decays into Higgs bosons might be a good way to look for something massive.</p>

<p>
While there are some theories that predict the existence of a particle that decays into Higgs bosons, having a theory in hand is not necessary. It’s enough to look for the particular signature, and, if it is found, we can then figure out what it means.</p>

<div id="attachment_36826" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignright">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Analyzers01.jpg" >
<img src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Analyzers01-300x156.jpg" alt="These U.S. physicists contributed to this analysis." width="300" height="156" class="size-medium wp-image-36826" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Analyzers01-300x156.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Analyzers01-768x400.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Analyzers01-1024x534.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/CMSResult160325_Analyzers01-250x130.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
These U.S. physicists contributed to this analysis.</p>
</div>

<p>
Accordingly, CMS scientists <a href="http://arxiv.org/pdf/1602.08762.pdf">
went looking</a>
 for events with these characteristics. Higgs bosons are unstable and preferentially decay into a bottom quark matter-antimatter pair. So what scientists were really looking for were events in which four bottom quarks were produced. When they found such an event, they used the energy and momentum of those four particles to see if they were consistent with making a pair of Higgs bosons.</p>

<p>
No excess was found (and, to be honest, more data is needed to say anything definitive). However, scientists were able to look for hypothetical particles with a mass of about 25 times heavier than the Higgs boson and twice as heavy as was possible with previous measurements. Even though nothing unexpected was discovered, the approach is an interesting one, and scientists are exploring more recent data recorded at even higher energy in the hopes that this approach might lead to a new discovery.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Wilson Hall building early morning</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/wilson-hall-building-early-morning/</link>

    <pubDate>
Fri, 25 Mar 2016 08:00:12 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[lshaddix]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=35509</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[A stately building on a gorgeous day makes for a pretty picture.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_35512" style="width: 2272px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-11_56e2e1a654583_WilsonHall3-11-2016.jpg">
<img class="size-full wp-image-35512" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-11_56e2e1a654583_WilsonHall3-11-2016.jpg" alt="A stately building on a gorgeous day makes for a pretty picture. Photo: Leticia Shaddix, PPD" width="2262" height="3074" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-11_56e2e1a654583_WilsonHall3-11-2016-221x300.jpg 221w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-11_56e2e1a654583_WilsonHall3-11-2016-768x1044.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-11_56e2e1a654583_WilsonHall3-11-2016-754x1024.jpg 754w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-11_56e2e1a654583_WilsonHall3-11-2016-450x612.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-11_56e2e1a654583_WilsonHall3-11-2016-184x250.jpg 184w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-11_56e2e1a654583_WilsonHall3-11-2016-300x408.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/2016-03-11_56e2e1a654583_WilsonHall3-11-2016.jpg 2262w" sizes="(max-width: 2262px) 100vw, 2262px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
A stately building on a gorgeous day makes for a pretty picture. Photo: Leticia Shaddix, PPD</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Strategic Collaborative Initiative Program</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/strategic-collaborative-initiative-program/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 24 Mar 2016 23:37:02 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[dstaszak]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=36781</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[I am pleased to announce the continuation of the Strategic Collaborative Initiative program that supports collaborative research projects between the University of Chicago faculty and either Argonne or Fermilab scientists/engineers, as well as three-way collaborations between University of Chicago, Argonne, and Fermilab. The Program: The University of Chicago funds research projects to support collaborative research between the university and the laboratory. Awards will be available for up to $75,000 (inclusive of indirect costs) for a period of 12 months. Criteria... <a class="more-link" href="http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/strategic-collaborative-initiative-program/">
 More &#187;</a>
]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
I am pleased to announce the continuation of the Strategic Collaborative Initiative program that supports collaborative research projects between the University of Chicago faculty and either Argonne or Fermilab scientists/engineers, as well as three-way collaborations between University of Chicago, Argonne, and Fermilab.</p>

<p>
The Program: The University of Chicago funds research projects to support collaborative research between the university and the laboratory. Awards will be available for up to $75,000 (inclusive of indirect costs) for a period of 12 months.</p>

<p>
Criteria for Proposal Selection: Criteria for selection include importance of the work to be accomplished, whether the collaboration creates a more powerful research program, and potential to achieve an ongoing collaboration between institutions. Proposals should align with emerging joint research priorities among the institutions. All proposals must include researchers from University of Chicago and Argonne or University of Chicago and Fermilab.</p>

<p>
Guidelines and Evaluation: Applications are due on Friday, April 15, 2016. Full proposal guidelines and application link can be found at: <a href="http://sci.uchicago.edu/">
http://sci.uchicago.edu/</a>
. A team of reviewers will assess the merits of all submitted proposals. The final selection will be made in June 2016. Upon completion of the grant period, funded PIs will be required to provide a brief written report on the project’s scientific results and how the funds were used.</p>

<p>
Additional questions should be directed to Meera Raja, Assistant Director of Research Innovation at <a href="mailto:mraja@uchicago.edu">
mraja@uchicago.edu</a>
 or Elena Zinchenko, Director of Research Innovation, at <a href="mailto:elenaz@uchicago.edu">
elenaz@uchicago.edu</a>
.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Video: Theoretical physics: insider&#8217;s tricks</title>

    <link>
https://youtu.be/TYTQm7t3I38</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 24 Mar 2016 20:34:39 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Video]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36784</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Theoretical particle physics employs very difficult mathematics, so difficult that it is impossible to solve the equations.  So scientists employ a mathematical technique called perturbation theory, which makes it possible to solve very difficult problems with very good precision. ]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[Theoretical particle physics employs very difficult mathematics, so difficult that it is impossible to solve the equations.  So scientists employ a mathematical technique called perturbation theory, which makes it possible to solve very difficult problems with very good precision. ]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Fermilab’s first Victor Blanco fellow: an NSHP partnership</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/fermilabs-first-victor-blanco-fellow-nshp-partnership/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 24 Mar 2016 20:22:20 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[From the Laboratory]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[News you need]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36766</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Fermilab has partnered with the National Society of Hispanic Physicists to bring talented students historically underrepresented in STEM to the lab.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_36772" style="width: 160px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/sandra-charles.jpg">
<img class="wp-image-36772" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/sandra-charles.jpg" alt="Sandra Charles" width="150" height="225" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
<center>
Sandra Charles</center>
</p>
</div>

<p>
Our efforts to cultivate a diverse workforce at the laboratory go beyond regular employees. The laboratory’s Diversity and Inclusion Office looks for ways to increase our recruitment of underrepresented minorities through internships and student programs, building a pipeline for a staff that more closely reflects the national population.</p>

<p>
To attract more Hispanic STEM talent to Fermilab, we recently established a relationship with the National Society of Hispanic Physicists, or NSHP, which runs the <a href="http://www.hispanicphysicists.org/StudentGateway/BlancoFellowships.html">
Victor Blanco Fellowship</a>
 program.</p>

<p>
I’m pleased to announce that our first Victor Blanco fellow will intern as part of Fermilab’s Summer Internships in Science and Technology, or SIST. Israel Chavarria, a junior in the University of Texas at El Paso physics program, will work with Fermilab scientist Juan Estrada on detector development for particle astrophysics.</p>

<p>
NSHP selects highly qualified students pursuing degrees in physics and astronomy to be Victor Blanco fellows. Now that we are partnering with the organization, NSHP will promote Fermilab’s internship programs to the fellows, putting forth the best candidates for our scientific programs. This provides Fermilab with a connection to a strong pool of potential interns historically underrepresented in STEM.</p>

<p>
Last year Juan accepted a D&amp;I Office request to speak at the annual SACNAS (Society for the Advancement of Chicanos and Native Americans in Science) conference, where he met NSHP President Jesus Pando, chair of DePaul University’s Physics Department. From that meeting and follow-up conversations, we’ve established this pilot, which will serve as the basis to write a more comprehensive proposal for the Victor Blanco Fellowship at Fermilab in the future.</p>

<p>
<a href="https://sist.fnal.gov/">
SIST</a>
 offers undergraduate sophomores and juniors majoring in physics, engineering, materials science, mathematics and computer science the opportunity to conduct research with Fermilab scientists and engineers.</p>

<p>
Israel’s internship is one example of many laboratory efforts under way to recruit and retain the knowledge, skills and abilities of a diverse talent pool. When our laboratory provides these kinds of opportunities to early-career scientists from underrepresented populations, our laboratory gains the benefits of an inclusive, more engaged and more insightful staff working to advance our mission.</p>

<p>
<em>
Sandra Charles is the head of the Fermilab</em>
<em>
 Diversity and Inclusion Office.</em>
</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
In memoriam: Euhel Campbell</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/memoriam-euhel-campbell/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 24 Mar 2016 13:44:03 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Milestone]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36475</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Former Fermilab employee Euhel J. Campbell, age 82, of Sweetwater, Tennessee, passed away on Tuesday, March 15, at his home. He was a technician in the Technical Division working on conventional magnet production. He worked at the laboratory from 1976 to 1998. Read Campbell&#8217;s obituary.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Former Fermilab employee Euhel J. Campbell, age 82, of Sweetwater, Tennessee, passed away on Tuesday, March 15, at his home. He was a technician in the Technical Division working on conventional magnet production. He worked at the laboratory from 1976 to 1998. Read <a href="http://www.kykerfuneralhomes.com/obituaries/Euhel-Campbell/#!/Obituary">
Campbell&#8217;s obituary</a>
.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Blackbird bath</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/blackbird-bath/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 24 Mar 2016 08:00:51 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=35989</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[A blackbird takes a shower on a recent wet day at the laboratory.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_35992" style="width: 730px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/blackbird-scroggins.jpg">
<img class="size-full wp-image-35992" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/blackbird-scroggins.jpg" alt="A blackbird takes a shower on a recent wet day at the laboratory. Photo: Amy Scroggins, Abri Credit Union" width="720" height="960" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/blackbird-scroggins-225x300.jpg 225w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/blackbird-scroggins-450x600.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/blackbird-scroggins-300x400.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/blackbird-scroggins.jpg 720w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
A blackbird takes a shower on a recent wet day at the laboratory. Photo: Amy Scroggins, Abri Credit Union</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Pushpa Bhat appointed secretary for International Committee for Future Accelerators</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/pushpa-bhat-new-secretary-international-committee-future-accelerators/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 23 Mar 2016 21:51:11 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Milestone]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=36256</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Pushpa Bhat begins five-year appointment as ICFA secreatry.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_33678" style="width: 160px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/08-0332-10D.jpg">
<img class="wp-image-33678" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/08-0332-10D-200x300.jpg" alt="Pushpalatha Bhat" width="150" height="225" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/08-0332-10D-200x300.jpg 200w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/08-0332-10D-682x1024.jpg 682w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
<center>
Pushpalatha Bhat</center>
</p>
</div>

<p>
Fermilab scientist Pushpalatha Bhat will take on a new role as Secretary of the International Committee for Future Accelerators, commonly known as ICFA. She takes over from Fermilab’s Roy Rubinstein, who steps down as ICFA secretary after 23 years. The Executive Committee of ICFA appointed Bhat for a five-year term.</p>

<p>
ICFA facilitates international collaboration in the construction and use of accelerators for high-energy physics. It promotes international collaboration in all phases of the construction and exploitation of very high -energy accelerators. It also facilitates the exchange of information on future plans for regional high-energy physics facilities and for the formulation of advice on joint studies and uses.</p>

<p>
Bhat is a senior scientist at Fermilab, deputy head of the Fermilab Program Planning Office, and an adjunct professor and graduate faculty member at Northern Illinois University. She joined Fermilab in 1989 and led numerous projects, including upgrades to the Tevatron accelerator complex, and contributed to the discovery and studies of the top quark. She joined the CMS collaboration at CERN in 2006 and there contributed to the discovery and studies of the Higgs boson.</p>

<p>
She is a fellow of the American Physical Society and the American Association for the Advancement of Science.</p>

<p>
&nbsp;</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Getting to Know Your Status &#8211; US immigration overview &#8211; rescheduled to April 22</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/getting-to-know-your-status-us-immigration-overview-rescheduled-to-april-22/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 23 Mar 2016 16:21:08 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[vstanley]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=36628</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The Visa Office will conduct a general overview of the US Immigration, presenting the information relevant to many international visitors and employees at Fermilab. This will be the first and most general in the series of increasingly detailed seminars, which will include presentations by the Visa Office staff and some outside immigration attorneys. Light refreshments will be provided. Please RSVP to the Visa Office at visaoffice@fnal.gov by Friday, April 15th.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
The Visa Office will conduct a general overview of the US Immigration, presenting the information relevant to many international visitors and employees at Fermilab. This will be the first and most general in the series of increasingly detailed seminars, which will include presentations by the Visa Office staff and some outside immigration attorneys. Light refreshments will be provided.</p>

<p>
Please RSVP to the Visa Office at <a href="http://visaoffice@fnal.gov">
visaoffice@fnal.gov </a>
by Friday, April 15th.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Small Group Training registration due March 28</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/small-group-training-registration-due-march-28/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 23 Mar 2016 16:19:13 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[jkoester]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=36625</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Small Group Training is a semi-private session in which a group of three individuals will train together under the guidance and supervision of a personal trainer to reach their goals in the most effective way possible. There are two Small Group Training classes offered. There is a 4pm class and a 5:30pm class. This class will be held twice a week on Mondays &#38; Wednesdays, April 4 – May 26 from 4:00-4:45pm or 5:30-6:15pm. Choose the time slot that works... <a class="more-link" href="http://news.fnal.gov/2016/03/small-group-training-registration-due-march-28/">
 More &#187;</a>
]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Small Group Training is a semi-private session in which a group of three individuals will train together under the guidance and supervision of a personal trainer to reach their goals in the most effective way possible.</p>

<p>
There are two Small Group Training classes offered. There is a 4pm class and a 5:30pm class. This class will be held twice a week on Mondays &amp; Wednesdays, April 4 – May 26 from 4:00-4:45pm or 5:30-6:15pm. Choose the time slot that works best for you. This class will meet in the Fitness Center and utilize the weight room and exercise room. Fee is $275 for 16 sessions of semi-private training.</p>

<p>
Register by March 28th in the Wellness Office, WH15W. For more info call Jeanne in the Wellness Office at <a href="http://jecker@fnal.gov">
jecker@fnal.gov </a>
or x2548. <a href="http://wdrs.fnal.gov/wellness/classes.html">
http://wdrs.fnal.gov/wellness/classes.html</a>
</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

  </channel>

</rss>
