<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  >


<channel>

  <title>
Fermilab at Work</title>

  <link href="http://news.fnal.gov/rss-faw" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

  <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

  <!-- Feed Logo (optional) -->

    <image>

      <url>
http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/themes/fermilab-newsroom/img/icons/fnal-logomark-blue.png</url>

      <title>

        The latest news from News Center.      </title>

      <link>
http://news.fnal.gov</link>

    </image>

  <description>
Fermilab news</description>


  <language>
en-US</language>

  <updatePeriod>
hourly</updatePeriod>

  <updateFrequency>
1</updateFrequency>

  <generator>
https://wordpress.org/?v=4.4.1</generator>

  <item>

    <title>
University of Chicago Innovation Fund information session</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/university-chicago-innovation-fund-information-session/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 21 Jan 2016 18:01:26 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[dstaszak]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=31103</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The University of Chicago Innovation Fund invests in early business development and proof-of-concept work for projects / ventures created by faculty, students, and staff. ]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
The University of Chicago Innovation Fund invests in early business development and proof-of-concept work for projects / ventures created by faculty, students, and staff. The Innovation Fund awards grants and invests in promising technologies and start-ups with high potential for societal and commercial impact, helping them to bridge the gap between basic research funding and commercial investment. The University of Chicago has committed to expanding the Fund to $20 million.</p>

<p>
In past cycles, the Innovation Fund has awarded funds ranging from $20,000 to $150,000. However, the committee considers any requests with a convincing case that funds will enable the team to reach a critical milestone, paving the way for commercialization, market validation, or external funding.</p>

<p>
The Innovation Fund will be hosting an information session at Fermilab National Accelerator Laboratory on February 23 in IARC, The Enterprise Room, at 3 p.m. Please RSVP by completing the following form: <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1jZ77uHcQdB_7zqTdrdXQq09rD5YKB-g0whQmuT-RPKM/viewform">
Innovation Fund Information Session RSVP</a>
.</p>

<p>
The deadline to apply for the Spring Cohort is Wednesday, March 9. Attached, please find a one page overview of the Innovation Fund, and you may apply online starting Monday, February 8, at the <a href="https://cie.uchicago.edu/innovation-fund">
Innovation Fund Application Website</a>
. Please contact Wolfgang Connell &#8211; Assistant Director, Programming, Chicago Innovation Exchange, <a href="mailto:wolfgangc16@uchicago.edu">
wolfgangc16@uchicago.edu</a>
 or sign up for an <a href="https://calendly.com/jpariso/innovation-fund-application-q-a/01-21-2016">
IF Application Q&amp;A meeting</a>
 (2/3 &#8211; 3/4) with the Director of the Fund.</p>

<p>
Read more in this <a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-21_56a11aeadbe55_IF-ApplicationPIOnePager-Spring16.pdf">
information sheet</a>
.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
IARC conference room name winner</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/iarc-conference-room-name-winner/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 21 Jan 2016 16:22:33 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[dstaszak]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=31046</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The new name of the IARC meeting room is [...drum roll...] Spark Chamber.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Aaron Sauers, OPTT, suggested the winning name for the meeting room in the IARC office suite. The name of the conference room is now the “Spark Chamber,” which is both a particle detector used in detecting electrically charged particles and also a clever reference to the spark of innovation that occurs with any new idea.</p>

<p>
Conference room names are being selected using a process blind to the people submitting the names. In this case the winner, Aaron, was a previous contest winner. (Well done Aaron!)</p>

<p>
To avoid any suggestion that “the fix was in,” Aaron graciously declined his prize and suggested we award it via a random name drawn from all the other participants in this contest. The winner of that drawing is Dr. David Neuffer from the Accelerator Physics Center who will receive a $100 gift certificate to Altiro Latin Fusion restaurant in Geneva.</p>

<p>
We are currently working on plans to outfit the IARC OTE 2nd floor with additional offices and conference rooms and look forward to more naming contests in the future. Meanwhile, a huge “Thank you!” to all of those who sent in your thoughtful, clever, and/or amusing suggestions!</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
TRAIN for Supervisors tutorial</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/train-supervisors-tutorial/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 21 Jan 2016 16:19:16 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[nicole]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=31052</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[You just received email saying that you need to complete an Individual Training Needs Assessment (ITNA) and a Work Activities Analysis Form (WAAF) for an employee you supervise. How do you do that again?]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
You just received email saying that you need to complete an Individual Training Needs Assessment (ITNA) and a Work Activities Analysis Form (WAAF) for an employee you supervise. Oh boy! How do you do that again?</p>

<p>
Don’t fret! The ESHQ Section has created a new tool to help you navigate and use the TRAIN system. This web-based tutorial will help with many different tasks in TRAIN including:</p>

<p>
• Performing and updating ITNAs</p>

<p>
• Performing a WAAF</p>

<p>
• Viewing employee training records</p>

<p>
• Finding and enrolling in training classes</p>

<p>
• Producing training reports You can access this new tool at <a href="http://www-esh.fnal.gov/ESH&amp;Q_Lectora/TRAIN_For_Supervisors/index.html">
http://www-esh.fnal.gov/ESH&amp;Q_Lectora/TRAIN_For_Supervisors/index.html</a>
.</p>

<p>
You can even submit a question if you don’t find the information you need: <a href="mailto:ESHTrainingGroup@fnal.gov">
ESHTrainingGroup@fnal.gov</a>
.</p>

<p>
Additionally, you are welcome to attend one of two scheduled lunchtime show and tell presentations in One West beginning at 12:00 p.m. on Thursday, January 28, or Wednesday, February 3. Accessing TRAIN is even easier now. Thanks to the recent change you may have read about in the former <em>
Fermilab Today</em>
, you can log onto TRAIN using your services username and password. KCA certificates are no longer required.</p>

<div id="attachment_31055" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-21_56a1018c05236_TRAINforSupervisorspic.png">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-31055" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-21_56a1018c05236_TRAINforSupervisorspic-300x190.png" alt="ESH&amp;Q's new TRAIN for Supervisors tutorial" width="300" height="190" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-21_56a1018c05236_TRAINforSupervisorspic-300x190.png 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-21_56a1018c05236_TRAINforSupervisorspic-768x486.png 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-21_56a1018c05236_TRAINforSupervisorspic-1024x648.png 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-21_56a1018c05236_TRAINforSupervisorspic-450x285.png 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-21_56a1018c05236_TRAINforSupervisorspic-250x158.png 250w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/2016-01-21_56a1018c05236_TRAINforSupervisorspic.png 1265w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
ESH&amp;Q&#8217;s new TRAIN for Supervisors tutorial</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Prescription safety eyewear program &#8211; off-site notification</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/prescription-safety-eyewear-program-off-site-notification/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 21 Jan 2016 14:25:08 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[crogers]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=31028</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Effective 1/26/16, the off-site vendor options will not longer be available. The on-site option remains available every Wednesday, 9:00 a.m.-Noon; Link: http://esh-docdb.fnal.gov/cgi-bin/RetrieveFile?docid=2313. If you have any questions regarding this announcement, please contact Mike Bonkalski.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
Effective 1/26/16, the off-site vendor options will not longer be available. The on-site option remains available every Wednesday, 9:00 a.m.-Noon; Link: <a href="http://esh-docdb.fnal.gov/cgi-bin/RetrieveFile?docid=2313">
http://esh-docdb.fnal.gov/cgi-bin/RetrieveFile?docid=2313</a>
. If you have any questions regarding this announcement, please contact Mike Bonkalski.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Anatine steam bath</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/anatine-steam-bath/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 21 Jan 2016 09:00:49 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Photo]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=30971</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[On this morning, in which temperatures were in the single digits, a gaggle of geese rested in the F Sector Pond string as moisture evaporated from the active cooling pond. What a day for a steam bath!]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_30974" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignright">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/geese-f-sector-pond.jpg" >
<img src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/geese-f-sector-pond-300x169.jpg" alt="On this morning, in which temperatures were in the single digits, a gaggle of geese rested in the F Sector Pond string as moisture evaporated from the active cooling pond. What a day for a steam bath! Photo: Maurice Ball, AD " width="300" height="169" class="size-medium wp-image-30974" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/geese-f-sector-pond-300x169.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/geese-f-sector-pond-768x432.jpg 768w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/geese-f-sector-pond-1024x576.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/geese-f-sector-pond-450x253.jpg 450w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/geese-f-sector-pond-250x141.jpg 250w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
On this morning, in which temperatures were in the single digits, a gaggle of geese rested in the F Sector Pond string as moisture evaporated from the active cooling pond. What a day for a steam bath! Photo: Maurice Ball, AD</p>
</div>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
One minute with Jemila Adetunji, ESH&#038;Q quality assurance specialist</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/one-minute-with-jemila-adetunji-eshq-quality-assurance-specialist/</link>

    <pubDate>
Thu, 21 Jan 2016 09:00:03 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=30515</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[Jemila Adetunji is a valuable member of Fermilab's quality assurance team.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<div id="attachment_30518" style="width: 310px" class="wp-caption alignleft">
<a href="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Jemila-Adetunji.jpg">
<img class="size-medium wp-image-30518" src="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Jemila-Adetunji-300x265.jpg" alt="Jemila Adetunji is a valuable member of Fermilab's quality assurance team. Photo: Rashmi Shivni" width="300" height="265" srcset="http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Jemila-Adetunji-300x265.jpg 300w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Jemila-Adetunji-1024x906.jpg 1024w, http://news.fnal.gov/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Jemila-Adetunji-450x398.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />
</a>
<p class="wp-caption-text">
Jemila Adetunji is a valuable member of Fermilab&#8217;s quality assurance team. Photo: Rashmi Shivni</p>
</div>

<p>
<strong>
How long have you been at Fermilab?</strong>
<br />

It will be two years in March. Time flies when you’re having fun!</p>

<p>
<strong>
What brought you to Fermilab?</strong>
<br />

Actually a colleague of mine in ESH&amp;Q and I used to spread “quality love” together in a different world. She came here, and then she recommended that I come here when they had an opening. Now we’re spreading quality love here at Fermilab!</p>

<p>
<strong>
What do you do here at Fermilab?</strong>
<br />

Within our group, we make sure the laboratory meets all of the DOE requirements with respect to quality. We assist, consult and help with process improvement, as well as manage issues in the tracking process.</p>

<p>
<strong>
What is your typical day like?</strong>
<br />

Every day is different. With quality we touch every organization from top to bottom, side to side. Depending on what comes up, I could be working on a task, helping a project with quality-related topics or assigned to an initiative. We also conduct audits and assessments.</p>

<p>
<strong>
Are there any projects that you’re currently working on that force you to think critically about quality and safety? </strong>
<br />

I’m working on an effort to understand what our site access and badging policies are. It spans across the lab campus, so the scope is huge. It’s not just about a process improvement but a change in cultural mindset. People follow something when they believe in it. It’s trying to sell all of that in one package. It’s a good challenge to have because it tests our abilities and helps us to grow to the next challenge.</p>

<p>
<strong>
How has this kind of environment changed your mindset on quality?</strong>
<br />

My background is in quality, but in a different capacity. I’ve worked in food industries, software, and paint and coatings. I’ve done different types of quality, and then I came here to a science-based and research facility where there is a different mindset and approach. At the end of the day, it’s still quality. It’s just a different application of it and working with different people, who are used to different things. It was interesting to have the opportunity to come here and try to shift the quality mentality a little bit. The good thing is that I’ve been exposed to a variety of different people prior to coming to the lab, and that has been beneficial to me.</p>

<p>
<strong>
What do you enjoy doing outside of work? </strong>
<br />

I like a lot of art – visual arts, performance arts, music. I love going to ballets, and I love watching orchestras at the Chicago Symphony Orchestra.</p>

<p>
<strong>
What advice or information do you think is important to share with the Fermilab community? </strong>
<br />

People have an idea that quality is like this nebulous, additional activity, but it’s in everything that we do. It’s not just about putting forth additional effort. Whether it’s work-related or outside of work, it’s about executing a process efficiently and keeping the customer in mind to meet or exceed their expectations.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
First neutrino results from NOvA submitted for publication</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/first-neutrino-results-from-nova-submitted-for-publication/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 20 Jan 2016 18:05:21 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Result]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=30992</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The NOvA experiment has submitted papers on its first measurements of electron neutrino appearance and muon neutrino disappearancde for publication in <em>
Physical Review Letters</em>
 and <em>
Physical Review D – Rapid Communications</em>
.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
The <a href="http://www-nova.fnal.gov/">
NOvA</a>
 experiment has submitted its papers “First measurement of electron neutrino appearance in NOvA” and “First measurement of muon-neutrino disappearance in NOvA” for publication in <em>
Physical Review Letters</em>
 and <em>
Physical Review D – Rapid Communications</em>
, respectively. The papers describe the key aspects of the experiment and the data analysis and formalize the results first presented last August.</p>

<p>
Using less than 10 percent of the planned eventual data set, NOvA predicts an observation of 218 muon neutrinos in the NOvA Far Detector in northern Minnesota in the absence of oscillations. However, it observes only 33 muon neutrinos, due to the effect of their oscillation into other types, in agreement with measurements from other experiments.</p>

<p>
In two independent analyses, NOvA observes six and 11 electron neutrinos produced from muon neutrino oscillations during the 500-mile-long trip from Fermilab to the NOvA Far Detector. Only one was expected had no oscillations occurred.</p>

<p>
These results provide new hints about the pattern of neutrino masses and the possibility that neutrinos behave differently than antineutrinos.</p>

<p>
The NOvA collaboration includes 210 scientists and engineers from 43 institutions in seven countries. Preprints of the <a href="http://arxiv.org/abs/1601.05037">
muon neutrino disappearance</a>
 and the <a href="http://arxiv.org/abs/1601.05022">
electron neutrino appearance</a>
 papers are posted at <a href="http://arxiv.org/">
arXiv.org</a>
.</p>

<p>
Read lay-language summaries of the <a href="http://news.fnal.gov/2015/08/muon-neutrinos-make-a-disappearance/">
muon neutrino</a>
 and <a href="http://news.fnal.gov/2015/08/nova-sees-electron-neutrinos/">
electron neutrino</a>
 results.</p>

<p>
<em>
Mark Messier, Indiana University, and Peter Shanahan, Fermilab, are co-spokespersons for NOvA.</em>
</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Is the neutrino its own antiparticle?</title>

    <link>
http://www.symmetrymagazine.org/article/is-the-neutrino-its-own-antiparticle</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 20 Jan 2016 17:50:01 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[leah]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Feature]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Story]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Symmetry]]>
</category>

		<category>
<![CDATA[Top News]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
http://news.fnal.gov/?p=30980</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The mysterious particle could hold the key to why matter won out over antimatter in the early universe.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[The mysterious particle could hold the key to why matter won out over antimatter in the early universe.]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Car for sale</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/car-for-sale-2/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 20 Jan 2016 16:30:44 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[torretta]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Classifieds]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=30965</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[2006 Hyundai Sonata, 4 doors sedan, blue, 128K miles, very good conditions inside, driver side mirror&#8217;s holder broken but mirror OK, a rust patch on the outside, $4200 negotiable, further details and pictures by request. Please call x3986 or email:torretta@fnal.gov.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
2006 Hyundai Sonata, 4 doors sedan, blue, 128K miles, very good conditions inside, driver side mirror&#8217;s holder broken but mirror OK, a rust patch on the outside, $4200 negotiable, further details and pictures by request. Please call x3986 or email:<a href="mailto:torretta@fnal.gov">
torretta@fnal.gov</a>
.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

    <item>

    <title>
Professional &#038; Organization Development 2016 winter/spring course schedule</title>

    <link>
http://news.fnal.gov/2016/01/professional-organization-development-2016-winterspring-course-schedule/</link>

    <pubDate>
Wed, 20 Jan 2016 14:10:25 +0000</pubDate>

    <creator>
<![CDATA[karlix]]>
</creator>

    		<category>
<![CDATA[Announcements and notices]]>
</category>


    <guid isPermaLink="false">
https://news.fnal.gov/?p=30943</guid>

                <description>
<![CDATA[The Office for Professional &#38; Organization Development 2016 winter/spring course schedule is available. The schedule includes management, professional development, technical and computing courses, including all Microsoft 2013 application courses. To view course descriptions and to enroll, please visit http://wdrs.fnal.gov/train-dev/index.htm. If you have a request for specialized training, contact Barbara Brooks x5021.]]>
</description>

                          <comment>
<![CDATA[<p>
The Office for Professional &amp; Organization Development 2016 winter/spring course schedule is available. The schedule includes management, professional development, technical and computing courses, including all Microsoft 2013 application courses. To view course descriptions and to enroll, please visit <a href="http://wdrs.fnal.gov/train-dev/index.htm">
http://wdrs.fnal.gov/train-dev/index.htm</a>
. If you have a request for specialized training, contact Barbara Brooks x5021.</p>

]]>
</comment>

                        </item>

  </channel>

</rss>
